<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Spicy World</title>
        <link>http://www.spicyworld.in</link>
        <description>Welcome to Spicy World by Arpita. Easy and Simple Recipes make your cooking faster and your food delicious.</description>
        <atom:link href="http://spicyworld.in/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chingri-malai-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chingri Macher Malai Curry / Prawn curry with Coconut Milk</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chingri-malai-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chingri-malai-curry.jpg' />Chingri Macher Malai Curry is a traditional Bengali recipe rather delicacy, where Golda Chingri or Lobster is cooked in onion - tomato gravy and then addition of coconut milk makes the curry more rich and creamy, thus the name 'malai curry'. Though I made it with jumbo shrimps as we both are not fan of lobster. Taste of this Prawn malai curry came out delicious, neither too spicy nor too sweet, perfectly balanced. I served it with mishti pulao aka basonti pulao and the pair was heavenly. Do try this recipe and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/aam-kasundi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Aam Kasundi / Mango Mustard Chutney</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/aam-kasundi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/aam-kasundi.jpg' />Aam Kasundi is a fire free recipe. You don't need to cook anything here. To make Bengali Aam Kasundi all you have to do is to blend everything in a blender and then for 2-3 days keep it under sunlight, after that in fridge. You can enjoy this preservative free Aam Kasundi all through the year. The aroma and taste of homemade Kasundi is phenomenal like any other Chutneys. I kept the recipe very simple and easy. You can not only serve this with deep fried food like Fish fry, Fish finger, Egg devil, all kinds of Pakora but also use it in Fish curry, Prawn curry or even Chicken recipes. During summer, Aam Kasundi is a must have and it uplifts the taste of so many simple things like 'saak bhaja' / stir fried greens. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/bhuna-chicken-wings.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Bhuna Chicken Wings / Slow cooked Indian Chicken Wings</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/bhuna-chicken-wings.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/bhuna-chicken-wings.jpg' />Who doesn't give order Chicken wings from starter menu in restaurants?? I am one crazy wings lover. There are so many yummy recipes of Chicken wings in the internet. They all look really good. Here is my take on Bhuna (slow cooked, using water as less as possible) Chicken wings which is basically Indian style spicy wings. You can make this recipe with drumsticks also. With some green chutney and onion slices they taste yummmmm! ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chanar-payesh.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chanar Payesh / Paneer Kheer</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chanar-payesh.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chanar-payesh.jpg' />Chanar Payesh is a traditional Bengali dessert recipe in which soft, crumbled panner will be cooked in semi thickened milk along with condensed milk and green cardamom. The texture of Chanar Payesh is very important - neither too thick nor too thin. In one word this Payesh tastes delicious and more over it is very easy to make. During summer, when you want to make some cold, lightly sweetened dessert for any occasion or party, then Chanar Payesh is the best option as it takes very less time to cook than other typical desserts.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/afghani-chicken-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Afghani Chicken Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/afghani-chicken-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/afghani-chicken-curry.jpg' />Afghani Chicken Curry is a very flavorful main course recipe in which marinated chicken will be first shallow fried until dark brown then cooked in a thick onion based gravy. I have learnt the recipe from my friend Ankita. The Afghani chicken tastes best with plain chapati or naan or light pulao. Try this recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-sandesh.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mango Sandesh / Aam Sondesh</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-sandesh.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mango-sandesh.jpg' />Can you imagine summer without mango? Mango is one of my favorite fruit with which you can make so many things like Yogurt, Ice cream, Phirni, Kheer, Cake, Cheesecake and what not. This season I made Mango Sondesh, taste and texture came out really good. You can make them with Ricotta cheese also, in that case add some milk powder as ricotta cheese is much thinner than Paneer. Mango pulp is going to give the Sandesh very refreshing and nice aroma. For color I have used saffron. Try this simple recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-kofta-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish Kofta Curry - party style !</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-kofta-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/macher-kofta-curry.jpg' />We all know what Kofta is. Kofta is almost like meatball but it is deep fried and light in weight. Last weekend one of my friend came over for dinner with her family. I cooked few dishes, one of them was this Fish Kofta Curry. Deep fried Fish balls will be cooked in a rich and creamy sauce. I got very positive feedback from everybody. Fish Kofta curry tastes awesome with fried rice, plain steamed rice or pulao. Try this delicious recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-bhapa.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Bhapa / Steamed Paneer in Mustard Poppy seeds gravy</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-bhapa.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-bhapa.jpg' />Paneer Bhapa is a very easy and flavorful Bengali veg dish which goes best with steamed rice. Bhapa means steamed. Any spicy bhapa dish like Chingri bhapa, Ilish bhapa etc will call for two important ingredients - Green chili and Mustard oil, without these two 'bhapa' will taste bland. In this Paneer Bhapa recipe, paneer will be steamed in mustard, poppy seeds, coconut and yogurt gravy within a steel box. The taste and texture of Paneer is out of the world. Try this very easy recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-bharta.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Bharta (Kolkata style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-bharta.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-bharta.jpg' />Chicken Bharta was prepared last weekend in our lunch. The recipe is Punjabi inspired Bengali dish. A very tasty shredded (pulled) chicken preparation which is famous throughout India. It has onion and tomato based gravy with beautiful flavor of kasuri methi and Garam masala. Of course, how can I forget about the Boiled Egg? To make an excellent Chicken Bharta you have to finish it off with boiled egg yolk. In Kolkata it's a frequently ordered dish in restaurants. To bring that exact flavor of restaurant I have used 'tandoori masala', believe me, do not skip this masala because it will definitely give the taste a big uplift. Chicken bharta goes very well with any rice preparation or naan, kulcha. But pair it with some naan or plain roti to enjoy it's authentic flavor.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/malai-chum-chum.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Malai Chum Chum / Lord Chom Chom</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/malai-chum-chum.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/malai-chum-chum.jpg' />You can find so many variety of Chum Chum recipe on internet. They all taste good, I can assure you that. Today what I am going to share is Kolkata special 'Lord Chom Chom' sweet recipe, in which cylindrical shaped Paneer will be cooked in sugar syrup then they will get a good coat of thick Malai (thickened milk) and Mawa (dried milk). In one word Chom Chom = a piece of heaven. Trust me I am not kidding! While staying in West Bengal, I have never made them in my kitchen. Because there are so many sweet shops where you can find them very easily. One lord chom chom costs around Rs. 15-20/-. If you follow this recipe step by step you will get very creamy and rich Malai Chum Chum which can be the show stopper of your next get together party.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-65.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken 65</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-65.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-65.jpg' />A super spicy and fiery indo-chinese starter is 'Chicken 65'. In southern part of India, few restaurants first started selling this Chicken 65 as a quick snack and now, people from all around the world knows about Chicken 65. In USA, we get delicious Chicken 65 from Indian restaurants, it is one of our favorite appetizer and that is why I made my mind to make this dish in my kitchen. You can make this with cauliflower, paneer or with several vegetables also. Every time the taste will be awesome! This yummy starter can also be served as cocktail snacks. In this particular recipe, do not compromise the spice level as it tastes best when it's fiery! A very easy dish with loads of flavor will always satisfy your appetite. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-potol.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Doi Potol / Dahi Parwal</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-potol.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/doi-potol.jpg' />Doi Potol is a traditional Bengali vegetarian delicacy. Potol is pointed gourd or parwal. In this recipe pointed gourd will be cooked in a spicy and tangy yogurt based sauce. I didn't use onion and garlic in this, but you can if you wish. Doi Potol goes best with plain steamed rice. I kept the recipe very simple and easy. Do try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-finger.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish Fingers (Kolkata style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-finger.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-finger.jpg' />If you are a fish lover, then 'fish fingers' should be on the top of your list. These crispy, spicy fingers can steal your heart in one bite. In Kolkata, every street food center, college canteens, restaurants sell these lip smacking Fish Fingers with chili sauce or Kasundi. You can use any kind of white fish fillet in this recipe. Oh boy, the taste is unbeatable and unforgettable !! There are no tricks and twists, the recipe is very simple and easy. You can serve them with tea, coke or a glass of beer. Believe me, these fingers can be the attraction of your next party. So, what are you waiting for??]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dimer Dalna  / Egg and Potato curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/egg-curry.jpg' />Dalna means a curry which contains potato with other vegetables or protein. But potato is a must for Dalna. Some also call it Torkari. Summer is coming and so is sweaty tiredness with it. If you don't want to spend long time in the kitchen, no worries! I have a solution. Dimer Dalna or Egg and Potato Curry is the most simple and easy recipe which can easily feed a crowd. Anyone can enjoy a good, tasty lunch or dinner with this comforting Egg curry and steamed rice without spending much time in kitchen. So, here is the detailed recipe for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-dum-biriyani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Dum Biriyani (Hyderabadi style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-dum-biriyani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-dum-biriyani.jpg' />I guess you all, who follow my blog, already know that we have a 'thing' for Biriyani. Be it with chicken / mutton / prawn we are always ready to enjoy. I've already posted Kolkata style biriyani recipe which is much easier than Hyderabadi style as you need to have full confidence on timing and proportions. In Kolkata we make the chicken with gravy first and then give 'dum' with cooked rice, whereas, in this case you have to spread cooked rice over the marinated raw meat and then give it 'dum' until the meat becomes perfectly cooked and also remain juicy enough - it's not easy as it sounds. After several trials I have achieved my confidence on making this biriyani and it's my pleasure to share the recipe + details with you. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sponge-rosogolla.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Bengali Sponge Rosogolla</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sponge-rosogolla.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sponge-rosogolla.jpg' />Rosogolla is cottage cheese balls cooked and soaked in suger syrup. Rosogolla is a Bengali delicacy. You will get so many flavors of them in Kolkata sweet shops, like Nolen gur / Rose / Mango / Strawberry / Paan / Cardamom and what not! But one of my favorite is Sponge Rosogolla which is plain and simple. They are literally light and soft like sponges! If you follow every tips of this recipe you will get the exact spongy Rasgulla. Being a Bengali it is my pleasure to share this recipe with you all. Do try in your kitchen and let me know how they turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-korma.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Korma</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-korma.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-korma.jpg' />Mutton korma is an old school and popular non veg main course item from Old Delhi. Any korma recipe has onion and yogurt based sauce, some even add nut paste also. Last weekend I had a party in my house. Among all the foods, the main attraction was Mutton Korma. Korma is very rich itself. Always serve this with light rice item or naan. Do give it a try and let me know how it turned out for you.
]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/niramish-aloo-dom.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Niramish aloor dom / Dum Aloo without Onion and Garlic</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/niramish-aloo-dom.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/niramish-aloo-dom.jpg' />Niramish means without onion and garlic. Usually when we offer a meal to god / goddess with our respect and devotion, we call it 'Bhog' / 'prasad' . In any prasad, this Aloor Dom is a must with khichdi and chutney. This recipe is without onion and garlic, that's why I mentioned 'niramish'. During monsoon you can also enjoy this with khichuri, beguni and chutney or in weekend breakfast make some luchi / lachha paratha with this curry. Whenever you arrange your next puja in your home, don't forget to put this item in the menu. I have already posted some other 'dum aloo' recipe. Try this in your kitchen and you will love it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/steamed-chicken-momo.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Steamed Chicken Momo</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/steamed-chicken-momo.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-momo.jpg' />One of the popular Tibetian delicacy is Momo. They are very similar to dumplings and now a well known street food across India. You will get so many varieties from modern MOMO shops like 'MOMO I AM', 'WOW MOMO' etc. Steamed chicken momos are healthy and tastes more delicious with hot and spicy <a href="momo-chutney.html">red chutney</a>. Thin wrapper made out of flour will be filled with tasty ground chicken filling, and then they will be steamed to perfection. You can enjoy them as brunch or snacks.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-momo.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Steamed Chicken Momo</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-momo.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-momo.jpg' />One of the popular Nepalese delicacy is Momo. They are very similar to dumplings. Chicken momos are healthy and tastes more delicious with hot and spicy chutney. Thin wrapper made out of flour will be filled with tasty ground chicken filling, and then they will be steamed to perfection. You can enjoy them as brunch or snacks.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/momo-chutney.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Momo's Chutney (smokey, hot and spicy)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/momo-chutney.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/momo-chutney.jpg' />Whats the fun in having Momos without chutney?sounds so boring. This red colored hot and spicy chutney has garlicky and roasted tomato flavor and tastes awesome not only with momos but you can pair it with samosas, kachoris, chicken pakoras etc. In few shops you will find 3 types of momo's chutney - red, yellow and white. But this red hot chutney is very common and popular all across India. Do try this recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mughlai-keema-paratha.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mughlai Keema Paratha / Moglai Porota</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mughlai-keema-paratha.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mughlai-keema-paratha.jpg' />Mughlai Keema Paratha is a very famous street food 
which has another name Keema Baida Roti. In Kolkata we call them 'moglai porota'. I made these parathas exactly like street style with minced meat, but you can skip that Keema part and keep the rest of the recipe same. The process is a bit lengthy but it is worth trying. I made dry potato curry along with mughlai paratha because these two goes very well with each other. I learned the recipe from my mother-in-law. She used to make this at evening without keema and we all enjoyed those very much. Here is the recipe with step by step clicks. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/hot-sour-soup.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Hot and Sour Soup</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/hot-sour-soup.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/hot-sour-soup.jpg' />Chicken Hot and Sour Soup is one of the popular soup variety from Chinese cuisine. In this silky, spicy, sour broth you can add almost everything like chicken, egg, tofu and many kinds of vegetable. Hot and sour soup tastes best (especially) during winter or monsoon and it can also uplift your taste buds. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/pancake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Indian Savory Pancake</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/pancake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/pancake.jpg' />Kids are always excited about their lunchbox. My mom used to make this savory pancake in my lunchbox and I loved them. You can also stuff the savory pancakes with any type of dry curry. Yesterday I made them in breakfast and they came out delicious. I mentioned 'savory' because usually we eat 'pancake' with sweet maple syrup but these can be serve with ketchup or chili sauce. Try this at your home and share your experience with me.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sunday-mutton-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sunday Mutton Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sunday-mutton-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sunday-mutton-curry.jpg' />Sunday mutton curry is a super easy, fuss free goat meat recipe which goes best with plain rice. This mutton curry is my family favorite and almost every sunday they demand to have it on lunch. And in the evening, my husband silently ask me is there any left over from lunch so that we can have it with roti at dinner? Yes, this sunday mutton curry is really close to our heart and we love it to the core. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely lunch with your family on sunday.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/lehsuni-daal-tadka.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Lehsuni Daal Tadka / Garlic flavored spicy Lentils</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/lehsuni-daal-tadka.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/lehsuni-daal-tadka.jpg' />Lehsuni Daal Tadka is a spicy toor lentil preparation which has a very flavorful garlicky tempering. This daal tadka goes best with plain chapati or rice. The recipe is very simple and easy. I usually make this lehsuni daal during winter as it tastes so good and seems comfort in a bowl in those chilly afternoons or nights. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-lollipop.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Lollipop</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-lollipop.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-lollipop.jpg' />Chicken Lollipop is one of the most frequently ordered starter item in Indian restaurants. Main trick here is to give chicken wings, lollipop shape. You can serve them after deep frying but trust me tossing the fried Chicken lollipops in spicy brown sauce will enhance the taste to another level. Do give this recipe a try and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/peas-kachori.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Koraishutir Kochuri / Green peas Kachori / Hare Matar ki Kachori</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/peas-kachori.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/peas-kachori.jpg' />Koraishuti means green peas and Koraishutir Kochuri is not just a food, it is an emotion for a Bengali. According to me, winter is incomplete without 'green peas'. Am I right ?? We Bengalis love to eat 'koraishutir kochuri' during winter. In my home nobody brings this kochuri from shops. My mom always makes this at home with 'aloo dom' , 'payesh' and everybody loves it. Nowadays we don't need to wait till winter for green peas because now almost everywhere frozen peas are available. I very much enjoy the combination of asafoetida (hing), ginger and green peas. This kochuri goes very well with 'kashmiri dum aloo'. Try this in your kitchen and share some of your winter stories with me.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dahi Chicken / Dahiwala Murgh / Doi Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/doi-chicken.jpg' />Dahi chicken is a very simple yet delicious chicken curry which goes best with roti or plain chapati. Dahi or Doi means plain full fat yogurt. This dahi wala murgh has a delicious thick white colored yogurt and onion based gravy. Well, I prefer white colored doi chicken, if you like colorful then add some turmeric powder and red chili powder, rest of the recipe will remain same. You will get very soft chicken pieces and tasty gravy from this recipe. Try this in your kitchen, let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dimer-chop.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dimer Chop / Egg Devil / Dimer Devil</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dimer-chop.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dimer-chop.jpg' />In Bengal, one of the famous street food is 'dimer devil'. Dim means Egg in Bengal. Nowadays, 'egg chop' is also served in many party, get to gather and occasions. To make this you have to wrap a boiled egg with spicy potato filling, roll them in bread crumbs and then deep fry them. In college canteen or any ceremony, sometimes the cook mix some minced mutton (keema) with the spicy potato, the taste becomes divine. But today I am sharing this recipe without keema. This yummy starter can be enjoyed with a cup of tea or a glass of beer. Try this in your kitchen and spend some quality time with Egg Devil and your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-bhurji-gravy.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Bhurji Gravy / Crumbled Cottage Cheese Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-bhurji-gravy.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-bhurji-gravy.jpg' />Paneer Bhurji is a delicious recipe of crumbled cottage cheese which goes best with plain chapati or paratha or pao. In this recipe, crumbled paneer will be cooked in onion, ginger, garlic, tomato based creamy sauce with some flavorful spices. This paneer bhurji gravy will take very less time to cook. Try this recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-handi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Handi</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-handi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-handi.jpg' />Mutton Handi is a delicious goat meat curry which has a scrumptious gravy and goes best with plain chapati, butter naan or pulao. Handi means clay pot. Usually mutton handi is cooked in clay pots, that's where the name came from. But I didn't have one, so cooked in my regular vessel. The taste was out of the world, soft pieces of slow cooked mutton literally stole my heart. If you are a mutton lover, please give this recipe a try and you can thank me later.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/quick-palak-paneer.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Quick Palak Paneer</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/quick-palak-paneer.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/quick-palak-paneer.jpg' />This palak paneer recipe is the best for weeknight dinner. Usually while making palak paneer, we need several kind of paste like onion paste, tomato puree, spinach paste, ginger garlic paste ... time consuming ! In this recipe everything will be stir fried in little amount of oil then we will make just one paste out of them. Creamy, tasty and buttery palak paneer will be ready in a jiffy ! Do give this recipe a try and let me know how it turned out for you. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-chicken-roll.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Egg Chicken Roll (Kolkata style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-chicken-roll.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/egg-chicken-roll.jpg' />I am a very fast food loving person. During college life there was hardly any day I skipped fast food. Be it simple 'phuchka' (panipuri) or heaviest roll, I was always in ! Surprisingly after my marriage I have taken a lot of control over my food habit, I have become more conscious now. But that doesn't mean I can't eat fast food once in a week .. hell I can ! and#128516;and#128516; When I made these yummy 'egg chicken roll' last of last week (after a decade) there was simply no alternative to my happiness. I found the taste exactly like those shop's ones what I used to eat during college days. If you are also a fast food loving person then treat yourself with one / two and#128540; of these (no one is judging) ! Look at those rolls ... how irresistible they are looking !!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/nolen-gurer-sondesh.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Nolen Gurer Sondesh / Date Palm Jaggery flavored Fudge</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/nolen-gurer-sondesh.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/nolen-gurer-sondesh.jpg' />In Bengal, we enjoy our winter with some signature food and sweets. One of the popular sweet is Nolen gurer Sondesh. Nolen gur is Date Palm Jaggery which is a very fragrant variety of Jaggery. Be it Gurer Rosogolla or Sondesh any Bengali can die for them. I kept the process very simple. So, go ahead enjoy the recipe with video and make them in your kitchen as soon possible.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-changezi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chatpata Chicken Changezi</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-changezi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-changezi.jpg' />Chicken Changezi has a rich, chatpata (spicy and tangy) and very delicious gravy which goes best with plain flatbread or naan. Changezi Chicken is a popular dish in Delhi. Almost every non veg restaurants and dhabas sell this dish. In this recipe lightly fried chicken will be cooked in a brown onion and nut based gravy and to make it chatpata, we will add chaat masala, lemon juice, green chilies and what not! Enjoy the recipe with video. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-tarka.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dhaba style Egg Tadka Daal / Dim Torka</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-tarka.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/egg-tarka.jpg' />'Torka-ruti' has always been a great favorite of mine. It's great with any type of bread like naan, tandoori roti, lachha paratha ... but with plain chapati / roti, the pair becomes heavenly. I have already posted some recipes on 'dhaba style' but the most popular and well known recipe is 'dim torka' or 'whole moong daal with scrambled egg'. When they serve this dish with raw onion chunks, green chilies and pickle, your appetite will increase to double for sure. From younger to elder, everyone is a fan of this dish. Make this easy recipe in your own kitchen and enjoy a great dinner with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/tandoori-prawn-pulao.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Tandoori Prawn Pulao</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/tandoori-prawn-pulao.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/tandoori-prawn-pulao.jpg' />Tandoori Prawn Pulao is a delicious, spicy seafood rice pilaf dish in which Prawns will be marinated with yogurt, tandoori spices and other ingredients then will be tossed with long grain Basmati rice ... so so good! You can have this Prawn Pulao as it is or any kind of gravy on the side will work just fine. The recipe is simple and take very less time to cook. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/nolen-gurer-payesh.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Nolen Gurer Payesh / Rice Pudding with Date Palm Jaggery</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/nolen-gurer-payesh.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/nolen-gurer-payesh.jpg' />'Payesh' / Rice pudding is a very common dessert in Bengal. Having payesh on any occasion is considered as a good sign. Nolen gur means Date Palm Jaggery which we get during winter season. The aroma and color of Nolen Gur is phenomenal. Sweet shops sell so many variety of sweets with date palm jaggery like - Gurer Rosogolla, Gurer Sondesh, Gurer Patisapta and what not! Payesh needs babysitting, as you have to reduce the milk to half of its quantity with patience, then cook the fragrant rice in that reduced milk and after that finish it off with date palm jaggery and raisins. Do try this recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned for you.  ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/hariyali-chicken-kabab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Hariyali Chicken Kabab</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/hariyali-chicken-kabab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/hariyali-chicken-kabab.jpg' />Hariyali Chicken Kabab is a very delicious variety of kabab in which boneless chicken will be marinated in yogurt, ginger, garlic, mint-coriander paste and lot of fresh spices along with few other ingredients. You can definitely use chicken legs instead of boneless. I will recommend you to use chicken thighs instead of breast pieces, as thighs will come out much more juicy. Hariyali means green color. The mint coriander paste will provide a nice green color along with an unique flavor to this dish. I have served Hariyali Chicken Kabab with Butter and Saffron flavored rice and Salads. Enjoy the recipe with video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kosha-aloor-dom.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kosha Aloor Dom / Bengali style Dry Potato Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kosha-aloor-dom.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kosha-aloor-dom.jpg' />Aloor Dom is a very good old Bengali recipe which can never go wrong with anything. You can serve this Bengali style dry Potato curry with Luchi / Porota / Kochuri / Pulao / Fried rice and what not. It tastes heavenly. I made Lachha Parathas to go with it. The recipe of Aloor dom is very easy in which potatoes will be cooked in onion tomato based gravy along with a special ground masala and yes, this freshly made ground spice is the main key to create the authentic taste of Aloor Dom. In winter grocery market will be filled with baby potatoes, this recipe will become more attractive if you can use them. Being a Bengali it is my pleasure to share this particular recipe with all of you lovely folks. It's time for you to enjoy the recipe with video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-keema-masala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dhaba style Keema Masala / Minced Mutton Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-keema-masala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaba-style-keema-masala.jpg' />In India many dhabas and restaurants sell Keema Masala which is minced mutton curry. Keema means mince. This is a delicious non veg gravy which goes best with plain chapati or naan. In Keema Masala, minced mutton will be cooked in a onion tomato based sauce along with some flavorful spices and lots of fresh green chilies and coriander leaves. Try this recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a wonderful dinner with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-fuchka.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Doi Fuchka / Dahi Puri Chaat</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-fuchka.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/doi-fuchka.jpg' />Doi Fuchka or Dahi Puri Chaat is one delicious and popular variety from Chaat Gharana. You can get several types of chaat in India from street vendors. They all are very very tasty. In Kolkata, one of the famous chaat is 'doi fuchka'. The hollow chips are filled with spicy potato filling, thick sweet and sour yogurt mixture, sweet tamarind chutney along with lots of fresh coriander leaves and few other ingredients. I have never made Chaat at home while staying in India because you can get them almost everywhere. But now that I am staying in USA, whenever I crave for Chaat, I had to make them at home. Trust me, after following this recipe you will achieve the exact same street style taste and flavors. Enjoy the video with detailed recipe. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chilli-fish.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kolkata style Chili Fish</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chilli-fish.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chilli-fish.jpg' />One of my favorite indo-chinese dish is 'Chili Fish' - which is very similar to Chili Chicken. In this recipe, deep fried fish nuggets will be cooked in a hot and spicy sauce with onions and peppers... so, so delicious ! You can get them in many Chinese restaurants in Kolkata. It tastes heavenly with fried rice or noodles and it is very easy to make. Try this recipe in your kitchen and enjoy with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-pakora.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Pakora / Cottage Cheese Nuggets</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-pakora.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-pakora.jpg' />Paneer Pakoras are delicious crispy vegetarian appetizer which can be served with mint or tamarind chutney and a cup of strong tea. I cut the paneer cubes from the center and filled it with green chutney as paneer has a bland taste. The recipe is very simple and easy. Your kids will love these Paneer Pakoras. Enjoy the recipe with detailed video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-malai-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Egg Malai Curry / Dimer Malaikari</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-malai-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/egg-malai-curry.jpg' />Egg Malai Curry is a Bengali delicacy, in which hard boiled eggs are cooked in a creamy milk based sauce. Dimer Malaikari is a very rich and mild curry which goes best with plain steamed rice or ruti. This is a kid friendly recipe, adjust the heat level according to their taste. They will enjoy this preparation to the core, I can vouch for that. If your family love egg, then you have to give this recipe a try. Enjoy the detailed recipe by watching the video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/pudina-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Pudina Chicken / Mint flavored Chicken Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/pudina-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/pudina-chicken.jpg' />Pudina Chicken has a delicious yogurt and mint based gravy which goes best with plain roti or Indian flatbread. Mint leaves / Pudina patta has it's very own unique taste and flavor, which is why you can only use them in those dishes where it fits properly. Not every chicken curry tastes good with mint but this one is my family favorite. Pudina Chicken is very simple recipe with loads of fresh flavor of mint, coriander leaves, green chilies and black pepper. They all sounds delicious together, aren't they ? Don't forget to serve few lachha pyaz / raw onion rings with this 'pudina chicken'. Now enjoy the recipe with detailed video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/hara-bhara-kabab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Hara Bhara Kabab / Green Vegetable Kabab</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/hara-bhara-kabab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/hara-bhara-kabab.jpg' />Hara Bhara Kabab is a delicious snack item for all the veggie lovers. Hara means green color. The kabab contains potato, spinach and any type of green colored vegetables like capsicums, beans and peas. Though I have only used spinach today but feel free to add other vegetables also. Like usual Kabab, it is not grilled but fried version. I kept the recipe as simple as possible. Just give it a try and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/rajasthani-laal-maas.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Rajasthani Laal Maas / Fiery Red Mutton Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/rajasthani-laal-maas.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/rajasthani-laal-maas.jpg' />Rajasthan is a state of India which is situated at the western part. In childhood I went there with my family on vacation, though I remember nothing much except our album photos. Rajasthan is the land of kings and 'laal maas', which is hot and spicy red colored mutton curry, is their well known dish. The dish is everything about color and flavors. They cook the mutton in a yogurt and onion based sauce with lots of chilies and garlicky flavor. The authentic Laal Maas recipe calls for 'mathania chilli' because they creat very nice red color with much less heat in gravy. Well, many of us don't have access to those chilies, so feel free to use kashmiri red chilies. Now, the recipe is very simple with loads of flavor, after all it's a mutton curry, it has to be delicious !]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/ghugni.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Ghugni / Yellow peas curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/ghugni.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/ghugni.jpg' />In Bengal, Durgapujo is incomplete without Ghugni. During pandal hopping one of the best selling street food after phuchka is Ghugni. Not only as a street food, on the auspicious day of Bijoya Doshomi (last day of durga pujo) Ghugni along with Nimki and Naru is served in every household of West Bengal. Ghugni is a yellow peas curry with few chunks of potato although many people add chopped fried coconut, that also tastes delicious. Ghugni is also served as an everyday breakfast along with bread or flatbread (ruti).]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-fried-rice.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Egg Fried Rice</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-fried-rice.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/egg-fried-rice.jpg' />Egg fried rice is a delicious variety of Indo-Chinese fried rices. It's a quick stir fry of rice, veggies and eggs with some seasonings and sauces. The best way to make Egg fried rice is by using left over rice and cooking on high flame, like many Chinese dishes. You can have this fried rice on its own or it can be paired with any manchurian gravy or chili chicken or chili paneer. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chingri-macher-kalia.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kosha Chingri Macher Kalia / Spicy Prawn Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chingri-macher-kalia.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chingri-macher-kalia.jpg' />I made this Kosha Chingri Macher Kalia last weekend with some steamed rice and curry leaves tempered musur daal. He finished the lunch (read there wasn't any meat curry, not even leftover) with a big smile, that too on weekend. This spicy prawn curry worked like a magic. So, I had to share with you all the recipe of this Bengali delicacy - kosha chingrir kalia. Though the word 'kosha' suggests slow cooking which we are not gonna do with prawns otherwise they will come out rubbery, but also suggests a dry (oily) and spicy gravy and in this recipe we will go with the second variety. Hope you will find the recipe interesting with the detailed video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-paneer-butter-masala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dhaba style Paneer Butter Masala</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-paneer-butter-masala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaba-style-paneer-butter-masala.jpg' />Paneer Butter Masala has a thick, creamy nut, onion and tomato based sauce with some juicy and lightly fried paneer pieces, also the rich gravy has an aromatic flavor of butter and kasuri methi (dry fenugreek leaves). Those who had 'dhaba' (street side food joints of India) food once in their life knows that no restaurant can replicate their rustic yet delicious taste. Dhaba style paneer butter masala can be served with butter naan, jeera rice, lachha paratha or plain chapati. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-kosha.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Kosha / Slow cooked Mutton curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-kosha.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-kosha.jpg' />Mutton Kosha is a Bengali delicacy which can be served with plain rice / basonti pulao / luchi. Mutton kosha requires patience, kosha means slow cooking in oil and spices. Off course to hurry up the process you can use pressure cooker, but slow cooking is recommended and this mutton curry like any other curry tastes better on next day. We have one more variance of the Mutton Curry called <a href="http://spicyworld.in/kosha-mangsho.html">Kosha Mangsho (Thakurbari style)</a>, you can also try that. Now its time for you to enjoy this recipe, lets start with the video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-kathi-roll.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Kathi Roll / Paneer Frankie</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-kathi-roll.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-kathi-roll.jpg' />Paneer Kathi Roll is loved by both vegetarian and non vegetarian people all across India. Paneer Frankie or roll is nothing but stuffed wrap, cooked paneer cubes with some onion slices and green chutney will be stuffed inside a cooked flour paratha.  It will be easy for you if you divide the recipe in 3 parts - making stuffing, making paratha, assembling the rolls. You can serve this as evening snack or brunch. This is a kid friendly recipe, just adjust the heat level according to their taste. Now its time for you to enjoy the recipe with detailed video.
]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-biriyani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kolkata style Chicken Biriyani / and#2458;and#2495;and#2453;and#2503;and#2472; and#2476;and#2495;and#2480;and#2495;and#2527;and#2494;and#2472;and#2495;</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-biriyani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-biriyani.jpg' />Kolkata style Chicken Dum Biriyani is one of the tastiest variety of biriyani recipe, which has awesome flavors and juicy chicken pieces. You can have it as it is or with Chicken Chaap / Korma / Kosha. I also have other Biriyani recipes in my blog. Cooking Biriyani is time consuming, also the more you practice the more you will get better at this. The process is lengthy but with few tricks and tips you can achieve exact restaurant like taste. In Kolkata, you can find the best Chicken Dum Biriyani at Arsalan, Aminia, Dada Boudi, Nizam's, Oudh and many other restaurants. Now lets enjoy the recipe with detailed video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/moving-to-usa-from-india.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Moving to USA from INDIA?</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/moving-to-usa-from-india.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/moving-to-usa-from-india.jpg' />Lot of my friends move to USA with their families, for short or long terms. This blog is going to help you in your initial days and for preparation for the movement. How do you really setup and what you do once you arrive USA? Every city in USA are well equipped with facilities and processes those similar to each other.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mughlai-chicken-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mughlai Chicken Curry / and#2478;and#2497;and#2456;and#2482;and#2494;and#2439; and#2458;and#2495;and#2453;and#2503;and#2472; and#2453;and#2494;and#2480;and#2495;</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mughlai-chicken-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mughlai-chicken-curry.jpg' />Mughlai chicken curry is a thick, nut based gravy dish from the Mughlai (awadhi) cuisine. The sauce of this Mughlai Chicken curry is very rich so you can serve this with naan, roti or light pulao. In this recipe first marinated chicken will be fried then cooked in onion, tomato gravy with lots of other flavorful ingredients. Last Saturday my family enjoyed it thoroughly, now its time for you to enjoy the detailed recipe with video.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/spicy-egg-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Spicy Egg Curry / and#2465;and#2495;and#2478; and#2453;and#2487;and#2494;</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/spicy-egg-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/spicy-egg-curry.jpg' />This is one of my favorite midweek curry so far. When you don't want to spend too much time in kitchen but still want to have something yummy, then this spicy egg (also called anda) curry is life saver. As you all know 'kosha' means slow cooking with oil and spices. I know what you are thinking - 'slow cooking' on weekdays?  When the main ingredient is egg, then yes you can make this Egg Kosha in a jiffy! It goes best with rice, but you can also have it with roti or paratha. Try this recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/upma.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Upma / and#2461;and#2494;and#2482; and#2488;and#2497;and#2460;and#2495;</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/upma.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/upma.jpg' />Upma is a very healthy and tasty Indian breakfast, in which the main ingredient is semolina. It is very popular in southern part of Indian. But nowadays Upma is served in many other households also. Almost twice in a week my mom used to give me 'jhal sooji'(Bengali term) in my lunchbox. It's not just me, my friends also enjoyed it. The fresh flavors of curry leaves and green chilies, proteins from lots of vegetables will always make this breakfast tasty and healthy. The recipe is very simple and easy. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/vegetable-chop.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Vegetable Chop / Vegetable Cutlets  / Beetroot Cutlets</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/vegetable-chop.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/vegetable-chop.jpg' />A cup of tea and some vegetable cutlets .... do you need anything more to spend a winter or rainy evening ?? I am always up for this kind of evenings. These cutlets are very much available in Kolkata. I guess, almost nobody makes vegetable cutlets at home in Bengal. On any occasion or just to enjoy some snacks, these chops were always bought from 'telebhajar dokan' / fast food center in my home. But in US, almost every Bengali knows how to make them. You can also make them in large quantity and then freeze them to enjoy afterwards. The recipe has no onion and no garlic, still yummy ...!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chilli-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chilli Chicken (Kolkata Style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chilli-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chilli-chicken.jpg' />I am a really big fan of indo-chinese food, whereas 'he' prefers mughlai or authentic bengali food more. Before marriage, I used to find excuses to go to any restaurant and eat 'chilli chicken' with rumali roti. I know what are you guys thinking. But don't know why I love this combo so much. In every street of Kolkata you can find various indo-chinese restaurants. I mentioned Kolkata style because they make this chilli chicken on a little bit of dry side and also extra spicy. You can also serve this as starter. Try this easy chilli chicken recipe in your kitchen and enjoy with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/daal-fry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Home style Daal fry / and#2456;and#2480;and#2507;and#2479;and#2492;and#2494; and#2465;and#2494;and#2482; and#2475;and#2509;and#2480;and#2494;and#2439; / Lentil soup with spicy Tempering</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/daal-fry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/daal-fry.jpg' />I fell in love with 'daal fry' when I first tasted it at a restaurant. A big bowl of daal fry with fresh aroma of coriander leaves and few slices of naan .. very simple equation to make me happy. Yes, you read it right .. no need of non veg stuff with this kind of blissful meal. In India, I never had daal fry at home, always in restaurant. But time flies so quickly. Now I can make it by myself. I didn't use onion and garlic as it was Tuesday, but you can definitely add them in oil while cooking. I have used only 'toor daal', you can use half 'masoor' and half 'toor' also. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely dinner with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/basonti-pulaao.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Basonti (or Basanti) Pulao / and#2476;and#2494;and#2488;and#2472;and#2509;and#2468;and#2496; and#2474;and#2507;and#2482;and#2494;and#2451; / Holud Pulao / Mishti Pulao</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/basonti-pulaao.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/basonti-pulaao.jpg' />This is a traditional bengali dish. 'Basanti' means yellow colour. You can also call this Sweet (mishti) Pulao. My mom make this in many gatherings along with <a href="macher-kalia.html">Macher Kalia</a> or <a href="mutton-kosha.html">Mutton Kosha</a>. I have literally no words about the combination. This is the must combination 'he' wants on his birthday. But once we had this with Chicken Dopyaza (already on blog) and that combo was also so good! Give it a try and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-aloo-palak.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dhaba style Aloo Palak / Potato cooked in Spinach gravy (and#2471;and#2494;and#2476;and#2494; and#2488;and#2509;and#2463;and#2494;and#2439;and#2482; and#2438;and#2482;and#2497; and#2474;and#2494;and#2482;and#2453;)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-aloo-palak.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaba-style-aloo-palak.jpg' />Whenever you read 'dhaba style' (street food joint style), you must be thinking that the recipe will be interesting ... right? Well, you are not wrong. This recipe is very, very exciting and creates exact taste of Dhabewali Aloo Palak. It is close to Palak Paneer recipe but slightly different and little low in calories. This dish goes best with plain chapati or naan. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-lassi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mango Lassi</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-lassi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mango-lassi.jpg' />During summer Mango Lassi is the best thing you can have. Lassi will soothen your body and tummy. Its kind of a smoothie but yogurt based drink. Sometimes after having a big glass of this you won't even need your lunch ... yes this drink is heavy, creamy and what not ! Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/himachali-rara-mutton.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Himachali Rara Mutton</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/himachali-rara-mutton.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/himachali-rara-mutton.jpg' />This dish was invented in dhabas from Himachal Pradesh. Nowadays it is available in almost every dhaba and restaurant. Its a very different recipe as it requires mutton pieces along with some minced mutton. Can you imagine that whenever you will scoop up some gravy with naan or roti there will be loads of Keema .... how delicious that sounds ! This dish goes best with Biriyani, Pulao and Butter naan. Try it in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/zafrani-pulao.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Zafrani Pulao</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/zafrani-pulao.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/zafrani-pulao.jpg' />Zafran which is Saffron is a very expensive and subtle spice. This pulao recipe requires lots of it as we are not using any other overpowering spices. It is a very easy recipe (best to feed a crowd) and goes very well with any type of gravy. Try this pulao in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-roll.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Egg Roll - Kolkata style / Bengali Breakfast Wrap (and#2465;and#2495;and#2478;and#2503;and#2480; and#2480;and#2507;and#2482;)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-roll.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/egg-roll.jpg' />One of the famous street food from Kolkata is 'egg roll'. A flaky paratha, a layer of egg and lots of veggies with sauces will never fail to satisfy your appetite. There are so many varities of roll like 'egg-chicken roll', 'mutton roll', 'paneer roll', 'egg-mutton roll' etc. They all are very yummy and easy to make. Try this in your kitchen and let me know about your story.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kochu-tato-root.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Golmorich Kochu / Taro root Pepper fry / Kalimirch Arbi</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kochu-tato-root.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kochu-tato-root.jpg' />One simple vegetable has so many names - kochu / arbi / taro root. My mom often makes this Golmorich kochu and our family, friends all love it. Whenever I go to ma's place, one of my demand is to have this dish. I don't feel the need of pairing it with anything like roti / rice. But you can have it with both. The recipe is very simple but don't underestimate the dish by its simplicity. First make it then let me know you like it or not.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-kosha.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Kosha / Kosha Murgir Mangsho</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-kosha.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-kosha.jpg' />In Bengal, one of the common non-veg curry is 'chicken kosha'. I think everybody is familiar with this name. Kosha / Bhuna is a process where you have to cook the meat with spices on medium - low flame in its own juices, if it gets dry then only add water as less as possible. It requires time but with chicken you can make it within an hour. One can make the same curry with mutton, potato, egg etc. They all tastes really delicious. I maintained the recipe very simple and easy. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/bengali-sukto.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Biyebarir Shukto / Bengali wedding style Mixed Vegetable</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/bengali-sukto.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/bengali-sukto.jpg' />Shukto is an emotion for a Bengali. Its a medley of bitter and sweet. The authentic Shukto recipe has no use of chilies. You can add various kinds of vegetable of your choice. Shukto is a must lunch item in Bengali weddings / functions. Now what is wedding style Shukto?? Well, its more creamy, more rich in flavor. If you can follow each steps of this recipe then you will get why I named it 'biyebarir shukto'.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/green-chili-mutton.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Green chili Mutton / Kanchalonka diye Mangsho</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/green-chili-mutton.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/green-chili-mutton.jpg' />This green chili mutton has become very popular nowadays in Bengali restaurants in Kolkata. They make this dish with chicken also. After reading the ingredients you will wonder why spinach leaves? 6 blanched spinach leaves wont spoil the taste, rather it will give the curry a nice green color. Heat will only come from green chilies that's why there is no use of dry red chilies in this recipe. It's a delicious curry and best for summer days. Do try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/tandoori-shrimp-tacos.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Tandoori Shrimp Tacos with Mango salsa and Raita</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/tandoori-shrimp-tacos.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/tandoori-shrimp-tacos.jpg' />The name itself sounds delicious ... isn't it ?? Tacos and Salsa are the part of Mexican cuisine. Nowadays many restaurants serve fusion food. This is an Indo - Mexican recipe. You can make it with chicken also. There are so many Taco recipes on the Internet. But my family fell for these fusion version where Tandoori Shrimps were wrapped in charred tortillas along with some spicy, tangy mango salsa and few drizzles of cooling raita. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-chow-mein-noodles.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Egg Chow Mein / Egg Noodles / Dim Chau</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-chow-mein-noodles.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/egg-chow-mein--noodles.jpg' />This easy noodles recipe is sure to make your lunch / dinner much better. With egg and veggies the noodles become more addictive and best option for lunch boxes. It used to be my frequent tiffin during school life. You can also add chicken and shrimp to this dish. I have '<a href="mix-noodles.html">Mix Noodles</a>' recipe already in my blog. Do try this delicious recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/beguni.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>How to prepare Beguni? (Crispy Eggplant Fritters)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/beguni.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/beguni.jpg' />We, Bengalis, call them 'beguni'. Some people call them 'baingan bhajji'. There is no difference among the names. This is all about the tastiness and chrunchiness. You can get this fritter with some puffed rice and green chili in Bengal from any 'choper dokan'/fast food centers. When they serve this in 'thonga'/paper bag, the feel and look always increase my appetite a bit.
Khichuri - Beguni or Daal - Bhaat - Beguni ... which combo should I make for lunch ? as I have picked two very beautiful eggplants from grocery store and he was constantly pushing me to make Beguni. As it was Friday Bong Eats uploaded '<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IzfEnYxzjUg">Kancha Moong Daal</a>' recipe and I just found my answer. Thanks to them for such a simple, yet tasty Daal recipe which goes very well with some steamed rice and Beguni. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/butter-garlic-chicken-stew.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>How to prepare Butter Garlic Chicken Stew?</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/butter-garlic-chicken-stew.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/butter-garlic-chicken-stew.jpg' />We all love to eat chicken stew during summer days ... right ? Because it is very healthy and soothing for our body. I gave this recipe a twist with a simple Butter Garlic tempering and the taste turned out so yummy. As I am a garlic loving person, so I didn't use any whole spices like Garam masala here because the garlicky flavor would have been dominated by those strong flavors. Give this super easy recipe a try and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sobji-daal-vegetable-lentils.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>How to make Sobji Daal / or Lentils with Vegetables</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sobji-daal-vegetable-lentils.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sobji-daal-vegetable-lentils.jpg' />'Sobji' means vegetables and 'daal' means lentils in Bengali. This is a very popular yellow Moong daal recipe which goes best with steamed rice. In Bengali weddings this daal is a must item for lunch. My husband is a fan of this dish. He doesn't even need any sides while having this particular daal and bhaat. Though I need something to go with it, so I have made few Beguni and my simple lunch became gorgeously delicious. Do try this one and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/bhapa-doi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Bhapa Aam Doi / Baked Mango Yogurt</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/bhapa-doi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/bhapa-doi.jpg' />"Doi" is a very popular dessert among Bengalis. But "bhapa doi" is a very traditional Bengali dessert. My grandma used to make this in pressure cooker and it tastes super delicious. My 1st compliment on this dish was "Bengali Cheesecake" from my man :) .... So, please try this and impress your family members.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/butter-chicken-roll.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Butter Chicken Roll</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/butter-chicken-roll.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/butter-chicken-roll.jpg' />I am one true lover of rolls, be it an Egg roll or Chicken roll. I know many of you do also. But fact is it's always better to have home cooked food than consuming street food, here everyone has one common complain about that - taste is not the same yaar ! right ? Being a crazy fast food lover I can guarantee you that this is one top notch recipe of Butter Chicken Roll. I've combined two best ideas (butter chicken and roll) in one recipe. With some left over butter chicken (post is up on the blog) you can create this incredible street style roll. So, from now on whenever you are making butter chicken, make some extra ... you know why!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/butter-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Butter Chicken / Murgh Makhani</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/butter-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/butter-chicken.jpg' />I have someone in my house who often demands to eat 'homemade-restaurant style' dinner in weekend ???. That's why last Sunday I had to make 'butter chicken' along with 'butter naan'. Nowadays 'butter chicken' is famous in all over the world. In Indian restaurants this is the mostly ordered dish. It has a tomato based, rich, velvety gravy and grilled, juicy chicken pieces. The combination was a total hit but you can also serve this with 'jeera rice', 'pulaao' or 'fried rice'. You can also make this dish with tandoori chicken, I have already post that recipe. Try this in your kitchen and serve a 'restaurant style dinner' to your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/cold-coffee.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Cold Coffee</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/cold-coffee.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/cold-coffee.jpg' />During summer Cold coffee is a must have. You can make this anytime and with minimum effort. My family is obsessed with it. I prepare this twice a week during summer. Do give this recipe a try and let me know how it turned for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-mastani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mango Mastani</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-mastani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mango-mastani.jpg' />This is a very popular recipe of mango: Mango Mastani. It has all sorts of goodness like mango pulp, fresh cream, vanilla ice cream and few other ingredients. I make this quite often in summer as it is very easy and effortless recipe. Do give this recipe a try and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-chingri-bata.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Aam Kasundi diye Chingri Bata / Prawn paste with Mango Mustard relish</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-chingri-bata.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mango-chingri-bata.jpg' />'Aam Kasundi' / Mango Mustard relish : the name itself is enough to make anyone's mouth watery, isn't it ? This delicious recipe of Chingri Mach (prawn) requires minimum time and effort to achieve its best taste. Fry everything in mustard oil and make a paste out of it ... perfect for summer ! Nobody likes to be in the kitchen for long in this hot weather. So go ahead, give this simple recipe a try and don't forget to share your feedback with me.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-chutney.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kancha Aamer Chutney / Raw Mango Chutney</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-chutney.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mango-chutney.jpg' />Summer is here and so are the mangoes. Yesterday I went for grocery shopping and market was filled with raw mangoes (kancha aam). Off course I bought few and immediately a request came from him : can we have 'aamer chutney' tomorrow?? So, before thinking of any other recipes with raw mango I had to make this Bengali style Mango Chutney. The recipe is our family favorite. This version of mango chutney is very cooling and soothing for your stomach and soul. Do try it in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sobji-macher-jhol-fish-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sobji diye Macher Jhol / Fish curry with Vegetables</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sobji-macher-jhol-fish-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sobji-macher-jhol-fish-curry.jpg' />'Sobji diye Macher Jhol' is nothing fancy in Bengali households. But we people have crazy obsession about it. Tollywood made a movie named 'Macher Jhol' ! So, being a Bengali I had to share this recipe with you all. You can make so many variations of this dish. Today I made it without onion and garlic, but you can surely add them if you want. One can also skip the vegetable part. Do try this easy recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dahi-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Doi Morich Murgi (Ma's recipe) / Yogurt Pepper Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dahi-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dahi-chicken.jpg' />"Lajawab" is the only compliment about mom's recipe. My mom make this dish in a very easy and simple way. But it tastes delicious. You will need very few ingredients for this dish. This the best recipe for teenagers because its very easy to make.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-fried-rice.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Fried Rice</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-fried-rice.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-fried-rice.jpg' />Fried rice is everybody's favourite .. agree or not ? You can add whatever ingredient you have in your fridge and thats what happened with me. I had few veggies laying around, so thought why not throw everything with some rice. Best part of this idea - added some chicken strips. After around 10 minutes of stir frying a good wholesome Chicken fried rice was waiting for me to make my soul and tummy happy. Now coming to the recipe, always use precooked, cold rice for this recipe and marinate the chicken strips in this way will provide the juiciest chicken pieces in your humble fried rice.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-chicken-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dhaba style Chicken Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-chicken-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaba-chicken-curry.jpg' />I know it's been two weeks I didn't post anything due to settling down in India, but heyy now I am back with another interesting recipe from 'dhaba' gharana. Every place has their own style of dhaba / road side food joints. Whenever we plan any short trip within Bengal, we try to make the lunch stop at some popular Dhaba. Their 'torka-ruti' and 'chicken curry' with rice are must for us. I like their chicken curry on little bit of thicker side, whereas the thin curry also tastes awesome. I made this delicious dish last month and we both enjoyed it with chapatis. Do try this easy recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.  ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/basic-chocolate-cake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Basic Chocolate Cake</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/basic-chocolate-cake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/basic-chocolate-cake.jpg' />Hey folks! I'm going back to India next week, that's why for few days I've been very busy with packing and all, regular blog post is also not happening ... very sorry for that but I hope you will understand. In Austin, this 'basic chocolate cake' will be my last post because tomorrow we will disconnect our internet. While cleaning the kitchen last week, I found half box of cocoa powder, half box of wheat flour, 2 sticks of butter and more than half box of sugar. With these ingredients what can be better than a basic recipe of 'chocolate cake'? And chocolate is always an addiction! I made it and frosted the cake with a super easy chocolate frosting. That delicious cake was our dessert for 1 week. Do try this in your kitchen and my next post will come after settling down in India ... so be patient and happy cooking!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/pav-bhaji.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Pav Bhaji</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/pav-bhaji.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/pav-bhaji.jpg' />Durga puja is just a few days away. Every street of Bengal and other parts of India will be filled with people and food stalls. Among all of them 'chaat' stalls are my favourite. I like various type of chaats like panipuri, dahi puri chat, papri chat, samosa chat, nimki chat, batata puri chat, ghugni chat and so on. Though today I am not sharing any Bengali chaat, but 'pav bhaji' is quite famous in Mumbai and many other parts of India. 'Bhaji' indicates spicy, tangy mashed vegetable curry and 'pav' means bread / bun. After having a plate of 'pav bhaji', don't ever forget to have a cup of milky tea ... trust me on this one. Before start cooking this dish, you have to remember one simple thing - Butter makes everything better ! Do try this recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a great evening with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-mutton-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dhaba style Mutton curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-mutton-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaba-mutton-curry.jpg' />We all love to eat food from Dhaba (road side food joint) while traveling. Nowadays you can find many fake dhabas and taste of their food is also fake, nowhere close to the authentic ones. Luckily few old and original dhabas in India still sells the best meals. After tasting those foods, you will probably think that their cooks must have some kind of magical hands. I once tasted their 'mutton curry' .... a rich, creamy, flavourful gravy and juicy, succulent meat pieces. Last weekend I recreated the same dish in my kitchen and surprisingly he said it tastes exactly like that dhaba's mutton curry and#128515;and#128524;. The recipe is very simple and easy to follow. Do try it at your home and enjoy a great lunch with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-rezala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Rezala</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-rezala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-rezala.jpg' />How many of you like the smell of 'capsicum' / green bell pepper in vegetarian dishes ?? I am. Whenever I cook, specially without onion and garlic dishes, most of the time I end up adding capsicum into it ... i know it sounds stupid but surprisingly the taste becomes more yumm ! Today's recipe is about 'paneer rezala', a vegetarian mughlai delicacy, where paneer cubes are cooked in a nut based white gravy and in that my very own addition is some fried capsicum. I made this last week for the first time and it has become one of our favourite. You can enjoy this with biriyani, pulao or some steamed rice. Do try this at your home and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/popcorn-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Popcorn Chicken </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/popcorn-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/popcorn-chicken.jpg' />In a rainy evening, a plate of hot, crispy popcorn chicken with a cup of tea / a glass of chilled beer can be seriously addictive! Yes today's blog is about 'popcorn chicken'. From younger to elder everybody loves this dish. This chicken recipe is very much different from 'chicken nuggets' or '<a href="chicken-pokora.html">chicken pakora</a>'. After frying them, you will get soft chicken inside and crispy coating (not breadcrumbs) outside ... guys, that is called perfection! Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a great evening with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mangsher-chop.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mangsher Chop / Mutton Croquettes </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mangsher-chop.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mangsher-chop.jpg' />Yesterday I experienced the worst ... my camera's memory card got corrupted and I lost more than half pictures of this recipe. We tried very hard to recover those photos but no luck!! It was nobody's fault, it's just that the tiny little piece of 'card' betrayed me and#128532;and#128532;and#128532; very harshly .. and I felt tremendously helpless towards 'technology'. Now you guys know why there is no step by step pictures in this recipe. Anyway, among all of this depression, the brightest side is the dish 'mangsher chop'. In Bengal, it is one of the popular and lip smacking snack which you can get in many fast food centers. Spicy, crumbly mutton filling inside and crispy coating outside. Here in Austin, it was pouring heavily from last 2 - 3 days and I couldn't find any better day than this to make those croquettes. You can pair them with a cup of tea or a can of beer, every-time they will taste better and better.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/tandoori-fish-tikka.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Tandoori Fish Tikka</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/tandoori-fish-tikka.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/tandoori-fish-tikka.jpg' />He bought a large packet of Tilapia fillets last week. He is a crazy fan of fish and can eat it everyday, whereas, I don't like to eat 'macher jhol' / 'mach vaja' each and every day like him. I get bored very quickly. So, this week I made these 'tandoori fish tikkas' along with some rice and simple daal. They came out delicious and also uplifted the taste of our boring lunch. I followed a very easy recipe to make these. Do try it at home and let me know how these tikkas turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-paneer-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chanar Dalna / Aloo Paneer curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-paneer-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/aloo-paneer-curry.jpg' />Chanar Dalna is a very hearty vegetarian preparation with simple ingredients. My mom used to serve this curry with '<a href="bengali-luchi.html">Luchi</a>' and the pair was heavenly. 'Chana' means curdled milk or homemade paneer and 'Dalna' means curry. Both of them are Bengali words. You can definitely make this dalna on any puja / vrat days as they are onion and garlic free. I have already shared '<a href="chanar-kalia.html">chanar kalia</a>' recipe with you all, but this one is much more simpler and hassle free than that. Try this recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a great lunch with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/morich-mangsho.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Black pepper Mutton Curry / Morich Mangsho / Gosht Kalimirch</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/morich-mangsho.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/morich-mangsho.jpg' />We both adore almost any type of mutton curry. I think, once in a week, mutton curry is must for every Bengali households. I made this curry with some plain roti / chapati in dinner last month, just didn't get time to post. Now finally I am sharing this yummy recipe with you all. If you love the strong flavour of black pepper, then believe me, 'morich mangsho' is worth giving a try. I am sure your tummy and heart will be happy after having this curry. So, let's get into the recipe ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sweet-spicy-chicken-bites.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sweet and Spicy Chicken Bites</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sweet-spicy-chicken-bites.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sweet-spicy-chicken.jpg' />Chicken Pakoras require no introduction. Specially when they are coated with a sweet and spicy sauce ... I love to eat them more than I love to eat any Chinese takeouts. It's a very kid friendly recipe and you can always control the heat level according to your little ones tastebuds. These tangy, spicy bites are more than yumm ! If you are having guest and you want to serve them a new starter then this is the best option for you. You can keep the fried pakoras in a covered bowl few times ahead, then just before serving lightly toss them in the sauce and ...... voila ! Do give this recipe a try and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/we-at-chicago.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>We at Chicago</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/we-at-chicago.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/trip-to-chicago.jpg' />Hey folks! I am back with another travel blog and obviously with a delicious food story from our recent trip to Chicago. During summer this city is full of fun! There are so many outdoor activities you can do, even with children. The streets were filled with people, road were badly crowded with bumper to bumper traffic, afternoon were real hot but overall the windy city has its own charm. I listed the name of every places and restaurants that we visited and enjoyed during our stay. It was 3 nights and 4 days trip and our experience was very good. If you don't have any plan for the summer, then just buy tickets and visit Chicago ... you and your children will have so much more fun there.  ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/launching-a-blog-website.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Launching a Blog / Website</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/launching-a-blog-website.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/web-hosting-essentials.jpg' />Let me take the opportunity to talk about launching/hosting a blog!!! Surprised?? Me too!!! I was looking for something when we moved to Austin, TX from Edison, NJ as I was feeling so alone as there are no good friends around. So kind of nagging everyday to him, then he told me "why not you start a cooking recipe blog?" I will not be selfish here, I am also interested about food and cooking, so quickly 'buy in' the idea. Now "he" wants to use his web designing knowledge to build a custom blog instead of using any open source tools. We are going to explain high level about the website launching and best practices.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-stew.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Bengali Chicken Stew</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-stew.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-stew.jpg' />During monsoon or winter or whenever you are down with cold and flu, this 'chicken stew' is the perfect dish to bring back the taste of your tastebuds. I am sure lots of Bengalis will relate to this dish. The slight heat from black pepper and saltiness of butter is the main attraction of this item. This stew is very healthy and home style as you can add many veggies of your choice. The recipe is super easy and I hope you will give it a try.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sabut-moong-daal.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Whole Moong Curry / Sabut Moong Daal Tadka</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sabut-moong-daal.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sabut-moong-daal.jpg' />How many of you guys clean your kitchen pantry often ? Well, I do it once / twice in a year .... very common for a super lazy person ! Last week I found half bag of whole moong daal in my pantry which was sitting behind a pack of pasta without whispering a word. Then I thought why not make a very simple daal like comfort food. Didn't get time to soak the lentils in water, that's why I used pressure cooker. But you have to try this recipe in your kitchen because it turned out very tasty without any hassle. I followed an easy recipe to make it, to go with plain rice and rotis.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/peshawari-mutton.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Peshawari Mutton</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/peshawari-mutton.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/peshawari-mutton.jpg' />Pakistani cuisine is full of delicious surprises. Their cuisine is lot more than just kababs and biriyani. I was searching for a different 'goat meat' recipe and suddenly came across with this delicious 'peshawari mutton' recipe. Don't know whether the cooking process is authentic or not, but I really fell for its simplicity. This dish doesn't require too many ingredients even though surprisingly it tastes unforgettably delicious. You can tell from the pictures that the gravy looks fantastic ! Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a great meal with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/food-review-yellowstone-las-vegas-trip.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Food Review!!! / Yes from our Yellowstone and Las Vegas Trip</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/food-review-yellowstone-las-vegas-trip.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/yellowstone-food-restaurant.jpg' />Finally I am uploading the food pictures, which we have enjoyed during our last trip to Yellowstone National Park. We went there at the end of May, it was a 7 days long trip. For me (as a food blogger) apart from trip, food has to be the second main attraction. From first day to last day of this trip, we had some delicious food and experiences. Let us share our experience with you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sorshe-chingri-bhapa.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sorshe Chingri Bhapa  / Steamed Prawn in Mustard gravy</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sorshe-chingri-bhapa.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sorshe-chingri-bhapa.jpg' />There are so many fish curry recipes in Bengali cuisine which calls for 'mustard' / sorshe, but this particular item is a jewel because you can cook this in microwave within 5 minutes.Yeaah you read it right ! With some steamed rice this 'sorshe chingri bhapa' tastes best. If you are a shrimp lover and also don't know about this dish, then trust me and give it a try ... you can thank me later ! ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/pheni-paratha.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Pheni Paratha / Shredded Flatbread</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/pheni-paratha.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/pheni-paratha.jpg' />I had no idea what this 'pheni paratha' is until one day I watched a video of this in YouTube and the end result was jaw dropping - so flaky and soft parathas ! Now the thing is they are not easy to make. You will need some patience and several trials to achieve the perfect texture of 'pheni parathas'. But these delicious breads are worth trying. I served '<a href="keema-aloo.html">Keema Aloo</a>' with these parathas and we both enjoyed the combo. Try this recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-tikka-masala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Tikka Masala</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-tikka-masala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-tikka-masala.jpg' />In USA, every Indian resturant serves 'chicken tikka masala' and it tastes delicious. I never had it in India, don't know why ? Tikka sized grilled chicken, onion and bell peppers are cooked in a tomato based creamy gravy. After tasting this dish several times in restaurants, last month I thought of making it at home. Few months ago I uploaded the recipe of '<a href="chicken-tikka-kebab.html">chicken tikka kabab</a>', so I am going to use that tikka spice powder in this dish. If you don't have the recipe, click the name and check it out. Try this easy and simple recipe in your kitchen and enjoy it with some butter naan and salads ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/maacher-jhuri.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Maacher Jhuri / Crumbled Fish curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/maacher-jhuri.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/maacher-jhuri.jpg' />This particular recipe calls for 'bombay duck fish' / loitta maach, but we couldn't get fresh bombay duck here, that's why I used rohu. 'Macher Jhuri' is nothing but a dry preparation of crumbled / mashed fish, which is typically bengali and goes best with steamed rice. Don't forget to add cubed potatoes because without them this curry will be totally incomplete. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/achaari-pulao.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Achaari Pulao  / Pickled Rice Pilaf </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/achaari-pulao.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/achaari-pulao.jpg' />I find this particular recipe of pulao very relaxing and different. 'Achaar' / pickle itself is a very tasty ingredient. With rice and some veggies it creates a very beautiful dish which takes so little time to cook. If you are looking for easy but unique weeknight dinner, then 'Achaari Pulao'  along with some raita and salads should be the one for you. This is a very flexible preparation, you can add any veggies / garbanzo beans or even some chicken pieces to the pulao. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a quick dinner with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/texas-bbq-experience.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Texas BBQ Experience / Long Weekend Fun with Food Day 2</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/texas-bbq-experience.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/texas-bbq-experience.jpg' />Texas is famous for the Barbecue, we keep on hearing this for long time!! We were planning to have it tasted to justify what we are hearing. We decided to use this 4th July long weekend to taste that. And once again it's Subhodip, our friend who found one of the best spot around the city. We truly enjoyed the BBQ. While coming back we also visited Radha Madhav Dham.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/second-bar-kitchen.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Second Bar and Kitchen / Long Weekend Fun with Food Day 1</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/second-bar-kitchen.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/second-bar-kitchen.jpg' />Long Weekend needs some activity and we are pretty much lazy this time, we never like to visit any place or go anywhere long in long weekends as its the time of the year where all the people go out, roads are crowded and hotels/airlines are pricy, so we decided to stay back this weekend a well but decided to enjoy the Food around the place so we hit Downtown Austin yesterday and our destination was <a onclick="ga('send', 'event', 'External Link', 'Click: Second Bar   Kitchen', this.href);" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" href="http://www.secondbarkitchen.com/">Second Bar and Kitchen</a>.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-dopyaza.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Dopyaza  / Chicken Curry with Doubled Onion </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-dopyaza.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-dopyaza.jpg' />Our common friend <a href="https://500px.com/subhodip" rel="nofollowed" target="_blank">Subhodip</a> visited our house last weekend for a dinner. He is a real foodie and have a very good knowledge about food and restaurants. So, I wanted to make something new on chicken for him and also for my blog. I have already posted 'mutton dopyaza' recipe, then I thought this time why not with chicken? Confirmed the idea with my hubby and 'chicken dopyaza' got selected for main-course along with 'mishti pulao'. They both gave me very positive reaction after finishing the dinner .... yaay and#128515; ! The recipe won't give you any stress, you can easily make them for big gatherings. If you are the host, then it's the perfect dish. The gravy is rich and very flavorful with juicy chicken pieces. 'Dopyaza' means you have to use double amount of onion - I used onion paste and cubed onion. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a delicious, fuss free dinner.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/panchmel-daal.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Panchmel Daal / Soup of Five lentils / Panchratan Daal</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/panchmel-daal.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/panchmel-daal.jpg' />Panchmel Daal is a very healthy and traditional Rajasthani dish, which you can make with five types of lentil - yellow moong, urad, masoor, toor, whole moong / chana daal. This daal is also known as 'panchkuti daal'. This dish is fully packed with protien and nutrition, also it requires very less oil. You can enjoy this delicious, thick consistancy daal with plain roti, bati or rice. Not only the flavour of spices but also the taste of those five lentils are unbeatable. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a healthy dinner with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/simple-khichdi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Simple Khichdi  / Bhoger Khichuri </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/simple-khichdi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/vegetable-khichdi.jpg' />After scorching heat of summer, first few days of monsoon are my favourite. In those days I don't like to stand in front of the gas for long time, because in the meantime you can enjoy the rain by sitting beside the window. I think you guys have already guessed that I am talking about one pot meal - they are so easy to cook. One of the famous one pot meal in Bengal is 'khichuri' / khichdi. I have posted several recipes on khichdi but 'bhoger khichuri' is the basic one. You can make this simple khichdi on 'puja' / vrat days as they are onion and garlic free. Don't expect this dish to be very rich or spicy, but to be very ordinary with full of taste. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/keema-aloo.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Keema Aloo / Minced Mutton Curry with Potatoes </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/keema-aloo.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/keema-aloo.jpg' />'Keema Aloo' is my favourite curry when it comes to a fuss free but yummy dinner. It's so rich and spicy that there is no other meat curry which you can make in such a less time. I used mutton keema but feel free to use chicken mince. After adding the cubed potatoes, this dish becomes a killer ! Serve this with plain rice or paratha, every time 'keema aloo' will be a hit. It is also a very good maincourse option for big party or any get together. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/panipuri-phuchka.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Panipuri / Phuchka / Golgappa</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/panipuri-phuchka.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kolkata-phuchka.jpg' />Most probably I am the only blogger who have taken so long to post about her own regional recipe of 'phuchka'. Because almost every blogger has their own regional recipe of 'panipuri / golgappa'. But it's better late than never. In Kolkata I never eat 'phuchka' with sweet chutney, always with tangy tamarind water and#128521; and believe me there is no fun of having them sweet, the taste has to be spicy and tangy. 'Phuchka' is nothing but hollow chips with spicy potato mixture in the center and then filled with tangy water. So, so, so good and tastes million bucks ! Every single description will be short in comparison to a plate of 'phuchka'. As I used store bought chips, so, I am sharing only the recipe of potato filling and tangy water. Try this any day in your kitchen and enjoy a great evening with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/pyaz-paratha.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Pyaz Paratha / Onion stuffed Flat Bread</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/pyaz-paratha.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/pyaz-paratha.jpg' />Onion parathas can be anyone's savior because they are very easy to make. I know that in many households people loves to eat 'paratha' in their breakfast. Only we know about the pain of making time-consuming breakfast. But these parathas are so simple and take very less time to cook. We both thoroughly enjoyed the spicy onion filling inside those soft parathas. You can make 5 parathas with these proportions and serve them with pickles, raita or veg / non veg curry. These parathas can also be served in lunch box. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a peaceful breakfast with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-kobiraji.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Kobiraji Cutlets  / Mutton Coverage (lacy)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-kobiraji.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-kobiraji.jpg' />Who doesn't crave for yummy snacks in the evening with some cold drinks during summer ?? I guess everybody does. Summer or winter doesn't matter ... weekend evenings are meant for some awesome starters ! After few trials I finally created the exact taste of Kolkata's one of the famous street food - 'kobiraji cutlet'. Kobiraji means coverage or lace like texture, which you can create with beaten egg. I know they are not at all healthy but they tastes insanely delicious. So, my advice - don't avoid them but eat once in three months and#128521;. I used minced mutton for this dish, you can also use minced chicken or fish fillets. Everytime you will fall in love with them after the first bite, believe me. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely evening with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-chop.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Macher Chop / Fish Croquettes / Fish Chop</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-chop.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/macher-chop.jpg' />We, Bengalis, love to eat fish in many forms. One of the popular snack of West Bengal is 'macher chop'. Spicy crumbled fish inside and crispy coating outside - scrumptious !! We both usually enjoy this snack in the evening along with a cup of tea or with a can of beer. Both combos are unbeatable. If you have to impress any Bengali ever in your life, just indulge him/her in 'Bikeler adda' (evening gossip), 'a cup of tea', Macher chop' and 'Rabindra sangeet'. I can gurantee he/she will request you to arrange another meeting soon ?. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a special evening with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kolhapuri-chicken-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kolhapuri Murgh Masala / Kolhapuri Chicken Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kolhapuri-chicken-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kolhapuri-chicken-curry.jpg' />Earlier I have shared the recipe of 'Kolhapuri Egg curry', today I am going to share the same recipe, but with chicken and some changes. One of the main ingredient in Maharashtrian cuisine is 'coconut'. We both are not too much coconut eater but when it comes to make authentic dish, I always try to make the taste as close as possible. As this is a 'Kolhapuri' gravy, you have to incorporate coconut. I didn't have fresh one that's why I used dried one. We both found the taste and flavour of the dish extremely delicious. The spicy gravy with sweet coconut flavour and juicy chicken pieces will take you to another world. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely dinner with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/gobi-manchurian.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Gobi Manchurian  / Cauliflower fritters in Brown sauce </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/gobi-manchurian.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/gobi-manchurian.jpg' />This dish is an indo-chinese item which is very popular and frequently ordered in restaurants of India. Gobi means cauliflower. The recipe is very similar to chicken manchurian (which I have already posted), except the key ingredient here is cauliflower, not chicken. You can make this dish with potatoes, soya granules or raw jackfruit also. Every single time it tastes delicious and goes best with fried rice or rumali roti. I made mine on dry side, but if you want this on gravy side, just add more water or vegetable stock. Both of them tastes incredible and you can serve them as starter or as maincourse also. Try this very easy recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-shawarma.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Shawarma in Pita pocket </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-shawarma.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-shawarma.jpg' />Though I ate various types of kabab in India but had no clue about 'chicken shawarma'. I tasted this delicious dish first time in Austin, Texas and now they are available in pretty much all over the world. Shawarma' is a middle eastern kabab preparation which can be made of lamb / chicken / turkey or beef. I had them first time with pilaf and second time with pita bread. My husband and I both fell in love with the second version and tried so many of them from different restaurants. Professionally 'shawarma' is made by stacking the seasoned meat on a spit and then roasted slowly in front of a flame for hours. At home we can't get that facility .. so don't worry, make them on tawa or flat pan and enjoy the same taste and texture of 'shawarma'.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/achari-khichdi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Achari Khichuri / Pickled Khichdi</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/achari-khichdi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/achari-khichdi.jpg' />'Khichuri' is a seasonal one-pot-meal. We generally enjoy it in monsoon or winter. The easiest dish of rice category is 'khichdi'. From bachelor to elder, everybody knows how to make it. But this is a tastiest variation of khichdi. 'Achar' means pickle, I used mango pickle here. The process is very simple, no need to fry or cook anything separately, everything will be cooked in one pot and one time. I made this on lunch along with some chips and fried potatoes. The combo was phenomenal and we just loved them.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/nature-with-canon.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>A Trip with Nature / Canon EOS Rebel T6i</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/nature-with-canon.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/nature-with-canon.jpg' />Travel is always exciting, and travel with a new camera is more exciting. We were thinking of buying a DSLR camera for our food blog and as we have planned week long trip was on it's way, we thought of buying the DSLR so that we can use the new camera for our trip. We always admire the beauty of the Nature and this time we are visiting the most wonderful places on the earth. Our trip consists of Yellowstone National Park, Grand Teton National Park, Bryce Canyon, Antelope Canyon and ends at ever exciting Las Vegas.
In this blog we are going to talk about the places we visited in past one week and the beauty of the Nature we enjoyed.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-ghugni.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mangsher Ghugni / Keema Ghugni / Yellow peas curry with minced Mutton</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-ghugni.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-ghugni.jpg' />Last week I was thinking that my blog doesn't have the recipe of 'mangsher ghugni' and being a Bengali I felt very awkward. There is no Bengali in the world who doesn't know about this dish ... yes, 'mutton ghugni' is that much famous. On special occasions or guest's arrival in evening, 'mangsher ghugni' is a very common item we Bengalis make. It's a Indian version of 'chili'. We make the curry of yellow peas with minced mutton .... delicious ! I kept the recipe very simple and easy. Try this awesome dish in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely evening with your loved ones. This is one of such things, which I always love at the time of Durga Puja Dasami when I visit my relatives house for Pranam, some families avoid keema but some of them use it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/french-toast.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Savory French Toast / Dim Pauruti</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/french-toast.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/french-toast.jpg' />Every place in this world has their own tea stalls and also some unique dishes. You can never match the taste of tea stall's food with big restaurant's food ... a huge difference !  One of the famous item of those stalls in India is 'toast'. You can get so many types of toast from them like 'butter toast', 'french toast', 'plain toast' etc. I love to eat 'dim pauruti' or in fancy words 'savory french toast' as snack with some ketchup. I used to take these toasts in my lunch box also. They are delicious and very easy to make. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chanar-kalia.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Curry of Cheese Balls / Chanar Kalia</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chanar-kalia.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chanar-kalia.jpg' />If your milk gets curdled, don't throw away, you can do a lot with it. Well, it's bengali style 'chanar kalia' where plain curdled milk / cheese balls are first deep  fried and then cooked in a tomato based gravy. It's a vegetarian delicacy of Bengali cuisine. The dish tastes awesome and goes best with plain basmati rice. In any puja or special occasion, we make this dish and it always becomes the attraction of the entire menu. I made this dish yesterday on lunch for the first time in my life and I pretty much nailed it. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-rezala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Rezala</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-rezala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-rezala.jpg' />This is a very popular dish from Mughlai cuisine in India. In this recipe medium size mutton pieces are cooked in a white, creamy, nut based rich gravy. 'Rezala' goes best with naan, biriyani, roti or paratha. I have already posted several recipe on 'rezala'. The dish has a very unique taste. It is neither very spicy nor very sweet. I made this last week and thoroughly enjoyed it with plain rice. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely dinner with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/bread-uttapam.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Bread Uttapam / Instant Bread Dosa</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/bread-uttapam.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/bread-uttapam.jpg' />I was drawn towards this dish because of its easy method of cooking. In weekdays I never manage my time to make 'breakfast', but when I found out about this recipe where dosa batter doesn't need any farmentation ... I was interested ! You just have to rest the batter for 10 minutes, after that you can make your delicious breakfast in no time. One of the famous south indian breakfast is 'uttapam'. They are very healthy and almost oil free. In this dish bread is the main ingredient and that's why the recipe is so simple. You can make plain uttapam or like me, you can top them with any topping of your choice. Try this easy breakfast recipe in your kitchen and spend your morning without any fuss !]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/hara-pulao.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Hara Pulao / Green Rice Pilaf</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/hara-pulao.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/hara-pulao.jpg' />'Pulao' plays a very significant role in Indian cuisine. Our cooking is mostly based upon 'curry' / gravy version which goes best with pulao. Their relationship is like - 'behind every tasty curry, there is a pulao' ... and#9786;and#65039;and#9786;and#65039; You can never underestimate it because sometimes 'pulao' itself can be very rich and attractive like 'yakhni pulao', 'prawn pulao', 'sweet pulao' and so on. Today I am sharing the recipe of 'hara pulao' which is the easiest and tastiest one. I flavoured the rice with a spicy green coriander paste and that's why the taste was damn good ! Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/murgh-methi-malai.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Murgh Methi Malai / Chicken cooked in creamy Fenugreek flavoured sauce</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/murgh-methi-malai.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/murgh-methi-malai.jpg' />This chicken curry belongs to the category of 'dhaba food'. The gravy is very popular in Punjab and all over India. You can also make this dish with paneer or vegetables. The white, creamy texture of the gravy and beautiful aroma of fenugreek leaves will take you to heaven. I used boneless chicken for this recipe, feel free to make it with chicken on bone, it will be no issue. You can pair this dish with plain chapatis, tandoori rotis or butter naan. Every pair will make your tummy happy. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a perfect dinner with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/bengali-luchi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Luchi / Bengali style Puri (Puffed Bread)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/bengali-luchi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/bengali-luchi.jpg' />Every family has their own breakfast story. In Bengali households, 'luchi' is the common one. Sunday mornings are meant for 'luchi - torkari'.  I was never a breakfast loving person, still not. Actually for me the toughest thing is time management in the morning, always hullabaloo ! But my husband is a huge fan of 'luchi' or 'kochuri', so I have to make it once or twice in a week. I have already shared many types of 'kachori' recipe with you and now is the time for some Bengali style Poori. You can pair this with any veg / non veg curry and sweets, every time 'luchi' tastes delicious. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a perfect breakfast on any Sunday morning.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/papaya-smoothie.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Papaya Smoothie</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/papaya-smoothie.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/papaya-smoothie.jpg' />Papaya is not new for any of us. We consume this fruit in both forms - raw and ripe. I love to eat ripe papaya as it is. They are so sweet and juicy, also very good for our health. Afternoons are so hot these days, almost every day I make smoothie with different type of fruits. Last week I made this 'papaya smoothie' and we loved it. It not only makes you cool but also works magically  for disturbed stomach. Try this easy smoothie in any summer afternoon and enjoy with your family ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaniya-murgh-kabab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Coriander Chicken Kabab  / Dhaniya Murgh Kabab </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaniya-murgh-kabab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaniya-murgh-kabab.jpg' />Few months back I saw a recipe of this 'dhaniya murgh kabab' with boneless chicken in facebook. The picture caught my eyes and then I made my mind to give it a try. But I actually got time to make it last weekend as I already had so many recipes in my drafts and to-do list. There were few changes I make with the recipe and we both got very much impressed by it's result. Smokey flavour of any type of kabab attracts me a lot. This time the flavour of fresh coriander leaves + roasted coriander powder made me real greedy. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy some scrumptious kabab with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kolhapuri-egg-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kolhapuri Egg (anda) Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kolhapuri-egg-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kolhapuri-egg-curry.jpg' />There are some recipes which are classics. They don't need any upgradation. 'Kolhapuri Egg Curry' is from this category. This is a famous Maharashtrian dish in which boiled eggs are cooked into the 'kolhapuri' gravy ... it tastes million bucks ! This curry is rich + hot in taste and goes perfectly with steamed rice or plain chapatis. You can keep a large batch of this Kolhapuri masala in fridge for almost a month. I will post a recipe on chicken with this masala soon. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a perfect dinner with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-mousse.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mango Mousse (Eggless)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-mousse.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mango-mousse.jpg' />Mango is all over the market nowadays. Everybody loves juiciness and sweetness of mango during summer. You can make so many desserts with mango. One of my favourite among them is 'maongo mousse'. Mousse has very light and fluffy texture that's why I love to eat it. Sometimes, to me, after having heavy meals rich dessert becomes overpowering, in those case 'mousse' is very good option. I made my mousse with mango puree and without egg, gelatin. With only three ingredients you can achieve such a lovely and quick dessert.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-roll.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish Roll (Kolkata Style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-roll.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-roll.jpg' />Bengalis love fish. We can eat fish in many forms like thick curry (kaliya), thin curry (jhol), batter fried, shallow fried (mach vaja), steamed version (vapa) and so on. One of the popular among them is 'fried fish'. Now in this category also we have so many variations. The most simple one is shallow fried marinated (with salt and turmeric) fish and the complicated one is 'Fish Roll'. In this recipe we stuff the marinated fish fillet with crumbly fish stuffing, then roll the fillet, coat with breadcrumbs and then deep fry them ... it's the example of our ultimate love towards fish and#128522;and#128522; . The hard part is making the roll, except that step, everything is easy. The taste of fish roll is phenomenal. You just need to give one bite to understand it's deliciousness. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-keema-paratha.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Keema Paratha / Stuffed Flat bread with minced Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-keema-paratha.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-keema-paratha.jpg' />Don't know about you, but I love 'keema' / mince form of meat. I have already posted so many recipes on 'keema' and this time I made paratha with mince chicken. The authentic recipe calls for 'mutton keema' but didn't have it that time, so made it with chicken and the parathas came out perfectly fine. These breads can be enjoyed with pickle, raita or any type of gravy. The recipe is very simple but you need to mince the chicken very fine like paste, otherwise paratha will not come out perfect. Try this recipe in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chaas-yogurt-smoothie.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chaas / Salted Yogurt Smoothie </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chaas-yogurt-smoothie.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chaas-yogurt-smoothie.jpg' />I love to keep 'yogurt' in my fridge all through the year. Because it has so many roles in cooking. You can eat plain yogurt, make gravy / cake / dessert / drink and also it helps to marinate protien. I can never imagine a day without yogurt in my fridge. Summer is almost here and I have already started to make different types of drinks and smoothies. Among them, one of my favourite is 'chaas'. This yogurt smoothie is salty, tangy and little spicy with loads of flavour. It helps to keep our body cool during summer. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/lehsuni-murgh-masala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Lehsuni Murgh Masala / Garlic flavoured Chicken curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/lehsuni-murgh-masala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/lehsuni-murgh-masala.jpg' />Are you a garlic loving person ? I am. As chicken is my favourite protien, so I had to combine these two in one dish. 'Lehsuni Murgh' is the perfect dinner choice I made last of last weekend. The dish has very minimum spices with beautiful roasted garlic flavour. This curry can be served with naan, roti or paratha. Recipe is very simple but it tastes heavenly.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-cutlet.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Cutlet (kolkata style) / and#2458;and#2495;and#2453;and#2503;and#2472; and#2453;and#2494;and#2463;and#2482;and#2503;and#2463;</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-cutlet.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-cutlet.jpg' />'Chop - Cutlet' shops are very much available in Kolkata. You will surely find one or two shop in every street. You know how much I love fried stuff, but this one sits on top of my favourite list. 'Cutlet' means breadcrumb coated fried flat croquette. Generally in India we eat this type of fast food from street shop. After my marriage my mom twice made these chicken cutlets at home. They were scrumptious and the taste was exactly like street shop's. I got the recipe from her and tried my hand on them last friday. Oh boy, they came out just perfect ! The recipe is not at all hard, it's very easy and quick. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/veg-mutton-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Vegetarian Mutton Curry / Niramish Mangshor Jhol</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/veg-mutton-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/veg-mutton-curry.jpg' />The name sounds odd ? Well, I am not crazy, we call this mutton curry vegetarian because it has no onion and garlic. The food we usually offer to our god / godess is called 'bhog' which never contains onion and garlic. During 'kalipuja' or diwali, we Bengalis make this vegetarian mutton curry with the meat of 'pathaboli' (ritual). The taste of this curry is suprisingly delicious, even if there is no onion and garlic. It's a very authentic Bengali lunch maincourse item which you can serve with steamed rice. The recipe is very easy but the taste is unbeatable.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-malai-kebab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Malai Kabab / Makhmali Murgh Kabab</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-malai-kebab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-malai-kebab.jpg' />What can I say about this one? Because again its Kabab!! This malai kabab has very smooth texture and smokey flavour. 'Malai' means cream, usually chicken cubes are marinated with yogurt, cheese, cream and some spices, I also did the same. You will be lost whenever you put that juicy, tendor piece of chicken in your mouth. I am damn sure that these kababs will make your appetite satisfy. Enjoy them with coke / beer or you can also make different types of wrap with them. You can never go wrong with these simple yet tasty kababs.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/begun-basonti.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Begun Basanti / Eggplant in Mustard sauce</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/begun-basonti.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/begun-basonti.jpg' />This is a very typical Bengali veg dish which you can only enjoy with steamed rice. We, bongs, have a very strong connection with 'posto' / poppy seeds and 'shorshe' or mustard seeds. We can creat so many delicious items with these two simple things. Now, 'he' is not a fan of eggplant, except fried version, to feed him this particular vegetable is really painful. I always have to make special dishes with eggplant, otherwise I end up eating all the eggplant and he finishes up rest of the curry, horrible ! So, last week I made this 'begun basonti' and do you know what happened ? He didn't make any fuss and finished up everything with a smile ... yaayy ! The taste of this eggplant gravy came out really good and I will make it again.
]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-pakora.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish Pakora / Deep fried Fish Nuggets</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-pakora.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-pakora.jpg' />I always find immense pleasure in cooking deep fried dishes, I know they are not always healthy to eat, but then, who is watching ?  I made this 'fish pokora' last month and simply forgot to post. It is close to 'amritsari fish fry' but I didn't use lots of spices, that's why they are just 'fish pakora'. You can enjoy this with chilli sauce / chutney / coke / beer. Everytime they will taste scrumptious. I have already posted ' chicken pakora' recipe but these fish nuggets take very less time to prep and cook. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-bhuna-masala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Bhuna Masala</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-bhuna-masala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-bhuna-masala.jpg' />Chicken curry is almost regular in my kitchen and that's why I always try to do some twists with the masala, otherwise who will eat same chicken curry regularly? Nobody ! This time I made the twist with dry spices. Generally whole garam masala is used in this type of curry but I decided to go for a change and surprisingly I got the perfect taste. 'Bhuna' means koshano / in low flame you have to cook something with spices for long time. The curry is very aromatic itself and goes very well with some steamed rice or naan. I will make this dish soon again, until then what are you waiting for?]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/cheese-stuffed-veggie-pops.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Cheese stuffed Veggie Pops</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/cheese-stuffed-veggie-pops.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/cheese-stuffed-veggie-pops.jpg' />We all love to eat fried stuff, right ? I know they are not that much healthy but still we do like them. I had lots of mushrooms in my fridge and couldn't find any interesting idea how to use them. Then suddenly I saw a picture of some beautifully golden colored veggie pops in google and I also remembered that I had cheese in my fridge. Then there was no confusion that I was going to make some cheese stuffed veggie pops. These pops can be enjoyed with ketchup by anybody, from kids to adults. Feel free to add any vegetable of your choice. After giving the first bite, those gooey melted cheese just blew my mind and thus, I had to share this yummy recipe with you. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/rustic-chicken-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Rustic Chicken Curry / Village style Chicken curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/rustic-chicken-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/rustic-chicken-curry.jpg' />I can eat chicken curry in any mood, any day. Chicken was almost regular to our home. My father and I are true chicken lover and that's why my mom used make very plain and simple chicken curry on weekdays. Sometime when she was in hurry, she used to throw everything in a pan and came up with this tasty chicken curry. I also heard that villagers often make this kind of curry which needs no recipe, no attention, but still a winner ! ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-ball-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish ball Curry / Macher Kofta Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-ball-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-ball-curry.jpg' />Cooking fried kofta / balls in a rich gravy is an old school Bengali delicacy. I guess everybody loves to eat fried balls made with paneer, vegetables, chicken, fish, mutton etc, but after soaking them in a flavouful gravy they become scrumptious. I had some fish fillets in my fridge and couldn't find any better idea than this to use them. Process of making 'Kofta Curry' is tricky and little bit of time consuming, but trust me, the combo of those gravy soaked dumplings with some steamed rice is just heavenly.  ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/pan-grilled-chicken-drumsticks.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Pan grilled Chicken Drumsticks </title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/pan-grilled-chicken-drumsticks.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/pan-grilled-chicken-drumsticks-.jpg' />It is a well known fact that we both are foodies. We are Bengali, so there is no escape from food and 'adda' (gossip). Every season, every puja and every occasion is incomplete without proper food to us. We love to do grocery shopping everyday in India. No guest can leave our house without atleast a sweet and a glass of water. So, I want to dedicate this post to them who really loves to eat and finds excuse to make special dishes even there is no occasion ! Everyone loves 'grilled chicken' and this one has done on skillet or pan so that everybody can cook even if you don't have any oven. The recipe is very simple but the taste is unbeatably delicious.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kheema-biriyani-minced-meat-biriyani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Keema Biriyani / Minced meat Biriyani</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kheema-biriyani-minced-meat-biriyani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kheema-biriyani-minced-meat-biriyani.jpg' />In India "biriyani" is a very popular dish and we both are crazy about any type of 'biriyani'. You can find plenty of variations in biriyani. The process is a little bit of lengthy but the result is unbelievable. Last friday I took an attempt on making Keema Biriyani, after the entire process I realized it is the easiest one. That is why I am sharing this recipe with you because it is one of the tastiest and easiest biriyani ever. Try this at your home and enjoy a lovely dinner.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-rogan-josh.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Rogan Josh (Kashmiri Pandit style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-rogan-josh.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-rogan-josh.jpg' />Mutton rogan josh is the signature dish of the Kashmiri cuisine which was bought by Mughals. 'Rogan' means oil / fat and 'josh' means intense heat. The dish is an aromatic mutton curry which is cooked in oil on high flame. It is slightly different than the usual mutton curries because of the usage of some unique dry seasonings. Rogan josh can be prepared in two ways - one with onion and garlic, the other one is with yogurt and without onion, garlic. Kashmiri pandits cook this dish by following the second method. I also tried the 'no onion, no garlic' recipe and the taste came out phenomenal. The gravy may seems super spicy but actually it is mildly spicy. The authentic recipe calls for dry ginger (saut) powder and 'ratanjot' (for red colour), I didn't have those so I have used some grated ginger and kashmiri red chilli powder. Do try this delicious mutton rogan josh recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a good meal with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sahi-paneer-korma.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sahi Paneer Korma  / Paneer cooked in creamy nut based sauce</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sahi-paneer-korma.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sahi-paneer-korma.jpg' />I have not grown up too much of eating 'paneer' rather I grew up eating fish, chicken, rice, dal and vegetable dishes. I ate paneer in parties and very few times in restaurants. But after coming to US I learned how to make paneer at home and trust me, those self made soft white cubes gave me immense happiness. So, after that day we both have become paneer lover and have tried several dishes. This 'sahi paneer korma' is another rich mughlai dish from Indian cuisine. In this dish the lightly fried paneer is cooked in a creamy nut based gravy which tastes heavenly with plain chapati or naan or pulao. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely dinner with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-tikki-mutton-keema.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Keema stuffed Aloo Tikki / Minced Mutton stuffed Potato Fritters</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-tikki-mutton-keema.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/aloo-tikki-mutton-keema.jpg' />Obviously they are not our regular 'aloor chop' / aloo tikki, they are something very special, aloo tikkis are stuffed with spicy minced meat, a little different from usual, but they tastes million bucks !! We Bengalis generally eat 'aloor chop' with puffed rice or tea whereas in other parts of India 'aloo tikki' is always served with chutneys. I will recommend you the second one for these stuffed tikkis as it enhances the taste of the entire dish. Now the ingredients of the stuffing are entirely up to you. I have used minced meat, but you can also use chicken, paneer, fish, lentils etc. Believe me, every time they will taste better and better. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy these delicious tikkis with coke or a glass of beer.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-rezala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Rezala</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-rezala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-rezala.jpg' />The maincourse dishes from 'mughlai cuisine' has rich, oily, flavorful gravy and my husband is a fan of their cuisine. One of our common favorite item is 'Chicken Rezala', thick + white + rich gravy with juicy chicken pieces. I like my rezala with thick gravy but many people also like to eat thin rezala gravy. I have already shared 'fish rezala' recipe with you and now it's time for chicken. You can make the white gravy in many ways but here I am sharing the easiest way and believe me, you won't find any difference in taste and flavor. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-manchurian.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Manchurian</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-manchurian.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-manchurian.jpg' />
            Whenever I buy different types of sauces from market, can't think anything but Chinese dishes. With few ingredients you can creat such a splendid item. So, last of last weekend I went ahead and made 'chicken manchurian', the more I can say about it's delicious tangy and spicy taste the less it seems. We enjoyed it with some fried rice but you can also serve this with hakka noodles or simple rumali rotis. I told you before that I just adore the combo of rumali roti and chinese maincourse dishes, don't know why ? Try this manchurian recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a restaurant style dinner with your loved ones.
      ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fulkopi-roast.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>White Cauliflower Curry / Fulkopir Roast (Kolkata Style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fulkopi-roast.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fulkopi-roast.jpg' />I have seen two types of cauliflower's roast curry from childhood, my mom makes the yellow + spicy version and the other one is white + sweet version. Both of them are my favourite but today I am sharing the recipe of second version because I have already shared a similar as 1st one cauliflower curry in my earlier post. So, in Bengal this cauliflower white curry becomes very popular during festivals and goes best with pulao or plain roti. Few pure Bengali restaurants serve this dish during puja. The recipe is quite similar with them except some changes like they make this curry with pure 'ghee' but I made it with oil + little ghee etc. The taste came out phenomenal and 'he' finished half of the curry in one sitting. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/coconut-cake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Soft Coconut Cake (Egg Less)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/coconut-cake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/coconut-cake.jpg' />I made last weekend another successful eggless cake and the flavour was 'coconut'. I have never used coconut before in cake batter but this time I do and result was 'scrumptious'. After making this, your heart will call for a bite to this moist cake and then a sip of warm tea ... aaaahh pure bliss ! If you are obsessed with coconut then treat yourself with a big piece of this eggless flaky coconut cake. I won't tell you about the beautiful aroma, because, to get that you have to make this cake !]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/spicy-dal.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Spicy Urad Dal / Jhal jhal Biulir Dal</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/spicy-dal.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/spicy-dal.jpg' />The best and most common weeknight's meal is dal and rice. Nobody likes to eat bland dal, everybody needs some zing to their comfort food sometimes. So, 'spicy urad dal' is my new favourite dal with some kick. You can also call this lentil soup 'tarke wali dal', now everyone has their own story of 'tempering'. I have used lots of garlic, fresh curry leaves, cumin and mustard seeds. But you can add any ingredients of your choice.Everytime it will taste better and better with some simple steamed rice and 'aloo vaja' / potato fries.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-kachori.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish Kachori / Macher Kochuri</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-kachori.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-kachori.jpg' />If fish is the right hand of our cooking, then 'kochuri' must be the left hand. Both of them are quintessential part of Bengali cuisine. Almost every weekend our breakfast has to be 'luchi' or 'kochuri' and on special day or maybe on guests arrival 'stuffed pooris' are inevitable. In this recipe soft and flaky pooris are stuffed with spicy, crumbled fish filling. After one bite, you can't resist yourself from having more. For this dish always use oily fish. So, whenever you are planning to make 'kochuri', try them with this spicy fish filling and enjoy a great meal.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/cauliflower-prawn-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Prawn Curry with Potato and Cauliflower / Aloo Fulkopi diye Chingri macher curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/cauliflower-prawn-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/prawn-curry.jpg' />This prawn curry is a family recipe and my mom-in-law is an expert of making it. It's a very common fish curry in Bengali households. We love to eat prawns in many forms, but his favorite is this one. I would suggest you to make this dish with small prawns, you will get much more flavours. First I fried the prawns, potato and cauliflowers, then cook them with gravy. Plain rice will go very well with this type of curry. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a good lunch with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-tikka-kebab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Tikka Kabab / Kebab</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-tikka-kebab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-tikka.jpg' />Do you have some boneless chicken, onion and capsicum in your kitchen?? Then why don't you make some 'tikkas'? Chicken Tikka is a very well known starter or kabab in India. Nowadays it also become popular in the whole world. You can make delicious gravy also with these tikkas. But first you have to make chicken tikka and here is the recipe ..  ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/lachha-paratha.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Lachha Paratha / Layered fried Bread</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/lachha-paratha.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/lachha-paratha.jpg' />In India one of the famous bread is 'lachha paratha', soft and flaky with lots of layers. You can pair almost any veg or non veg gravy with this paratha, everytime they will taste awesome. For novice, this type of paratha may not be successful on first attempt. But believe me, after few try they will seem very easy.  The main attraction here is the layers. The more layers you can make, the more flaky paratha you will get. Try this recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a special dinner with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-pizza.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Pizza with Makhni sauce</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-pizza.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-pizza.jpg' />Ahhh, atlast I got the time to write down this particular. Made this Chicken Pizza two months ago with Makhni gravy, but the recipe is a bit long, so didn't get the time to write in one sitting. Finally I am posting the delicious pizza recipe. The main attraction here is the sauce which is makhni gravy. I know that we all are a big fan of 'murg makhni' or 'paneer makhni', then why not try this sauce with pizza ?? This recipe will give you a very satisfying result.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-fry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish Fry (Kolkata Style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-fry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-fry.jpg' />There is a fast food center in Chandannagar, named 'robi fast food center', to me he is the best fish fry maker. As my school was in Chandannagar, I know more shops of there than Chinsurah. There are actually two famous shops - 'bolai' is famous for 'chicken pokora' and 'robi' is famous for 'fish fry'. He always make them in front of you, deep fry them in hot oil and then serve those fries with salad and kasundi. Ohh, I miss those foods and fun a lot here. You will enjoy soft, flaky fish inside and crispy, crunchy coating outside, just heavenly. I brought that exact taste and flavour straight from his shop to my kitchen. Try this easy recipe in your kitchen and enjoy !!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/masala-chai.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Masala Chai / Indian spiced Tea</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/masala-chai.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/masala-chai.jpg' />I think without a cup of tea every day is incomplete. Don't you think so ?? Tea plays a very important role in our life. In the morning my father needs a cup of tea, a biscuit and a newspaper. I guess every household has the same story in India. To me every gossip and get to gather is incomplete without tea. Every country has their own taste of tea. Here is the recipe of our Indian special 'masala chai' ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-maach.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish curry with yogurt / Doi Maach</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-maach.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/doi-maach.jpg' />We bengalis usually eat 3-4 items with rice in lunch. Yess, its the family tradition in every household in Bengal. Whereas in USA, either it's lunch or dinner, I always make one curry with rice or roti. Sometimes I wonder how our moms, grand mas and mom-in-laws gets time to cook so many items. 'Doi Maach' is an another tasty bengali fish curry which goes very well with steamed rice. It's a classic and traditional dish, in which the fried fishes are cooked in yogurt based flavourful gravy. Try this easy fish curry recipe in your kitchen and enjoy a perfect lunch with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/tres-leches.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chocolate Tres Leches Cake / 3 Milk Chocolate Cake (Eggless)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/tres-leches.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/tres-leches.jpg' />In Austin winter has already started melting down. Specially at afternoon hot dry air and sunlight starts forcing us to say 'goodbye' to winter. The season of sweating and thirsting is almost waiting on our doorstep. But we can always make suitable and comfortable food for any kind of season. 'Tres Leches' (Spanish word) cake is the perfect chilled dessert for summer. In this recipe an eggless cake will be soaked in 3 types of milk (whole milk, condensed milk and heavy cream) and the special addition will be Chocolate. Don't worry, the cake won't be 'too much' soggy. You can keep it in fridge upto 7 days. Want to know what is the best part?? I am writing about 'tres leches' and also having it right now !!!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chocolate-squares.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chocolate Cake Squares (Vegan)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chocolate-squares.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chocolate-squares.jpg' />I wanted to make a vegan chocolate cake but ended up with these fluffy squares. This type of incident happens a lot with me. Actually I made the batter in less quantity with comparison of my baking tray. So, after successful baking, length of the cake was thin. The whole round was not photogenic, but don't you think these squares are too cute ?? Well, sometimes it's better to give some last moment twists in your regular recipes. This cake has no egg, no butter and no milk. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy some guilt free chocolate cake with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/marble-cake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Marble Cake</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/marble-cake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/marble-cake.jpg' />This is my third successful cake on first attempt. To make 'marble cake' you will need two flavours. I have used most common two flavours - vanilla and chocolate. You can use any flavours of your choice. The texture of this cake impressed me a lot. Just love to bite those chocolate swirls with vanilla sponge.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/prawn-biriyani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Prawn Biriyani / Shrimp Biriyani / Chingrir Pulao</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/prawn-biriyani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/prawn-biriyani.jpg' />This is my first try on 'Prawn Biriyani' and I pretty much nailed it. I have made this biriyani in classic way, everything is cooked by 'dum' and also in sealed vessel. The taste and aroma was phenomenal. The flavour of fresh shrimps and long grain basmati rice gave this dish a unique taste, very much different from chicken / mutton biriyani. We both enjoyed it with chicken curry. You have to try this biriyani in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/vanilla-sponge-cake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Vanilla Sponge Cake (No Fat)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/vanilla-sponge-cake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/vanilla-sponge-cake.jpg' />I am a beginner in the baking world. 'Vanilla sponge Cake' without oil and butter is my second successful cake. The taste was quite good and I was really impressed by its texture. In this sponge cake the key ingredient is egg. Egg whites will make this cake spongy and fluffy. You can enjoy it as snack or with a cup of tea.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-pulao-yakhni-pulao.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Pulao / Yakhni Pulao</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-pulao-yakhni-pulao.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-pulao-yakhni-pulao.jpg' />A good Indian maincourse dish is always paired well with various types of pulao or many types of bread. But sometimes pulao itself can become a very rich and heavy dish. Yes, I am talking about 'mutton pulao'. In this recipe, the rice will be cooked with the tasty mutton stock (yakhni). That is why this type of pulao become rich itself. We both are very much fond of 'yakhni pulao'. You just have to be perfect about the measurement. Try this in your kitchen and make your tummy happy !!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/palak-paneer.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Palak Paneer</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/palak-paneer.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/palak-paneer.jpg' />'Palak paneer' is a famous north indian dish. This is a hit item for spinach lovers. After adding heavy cream the texture will make you greedy. Palak paneer's smooth, rich and velvety gravy is beyond everything. It goes very well with butter naan. It's a no onion and no garlic recipe]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/brownie.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chocolate Brownies using Brownie Mix</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/brownie.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/brownie.jpg' />I am not a fan of dessert, but do love cakes and brownies. Some of my friends are always preparing desserts and that always keep inspiring me, so this time I thought of preparing something. As this was my first time on brownie, didn't want to take any risk. So, I've made these chocolate brownies with 'Betty Crockers' brownie mix. The result was fantastic 'he' didn't find any difference between these homemade and store bought. Within two days my all brownies were finished. If you want to serve them warm, then pair them with a glass of chilled milk, every kid will love the pairing. Try this easy brownies in your kitchen and let me know how they turned out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/ulta-biriyani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Ulta Biriyani / Upside down Chicken Biriyani / Indian style Maqlooba</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/ulta-biriyani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/maqlooba.jpg' />My husband is a craaaazzyyyyy BiriYani lover. So, I thought what could be more exciting than a biriyani treat to him on V day!!! To cook something special, what he loves, will be the perfect way to express my feelings to him on this perfect day. I researched a lot upon new ideas of biriyani, then my eyes got stuck on Chef Sanjay Thumma's 'ulta biriyani'- how beautiful it is!! I won't say that this is the authentic Arabian 'Maqlooba' because their cooking process and recipe are slightly different than ours. Anyway, I was searching for some new ideas and then found one. I was also impressed by its recipe, it's a one pot biriyani. You don't have to spend half of your day in kitchen making biriyani, the dish will take just an hour. This biriyani has soft, juicy chicken pieces, beautiful long grain rice and some mild flavours. Try this easy peasy upside down Chicken Biriyani in your kitchen and enjoy a perfect dinner with your (biriyani loving) partner ]]>&#x1f609;<![CDATA[]]>&#x1f609;<![CDATA[ ...
      ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/jeera-rice.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Jeera Rice / Jeera Pulao</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/jeera-rice.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/jeera-rice.jpg' />I am a big fan of different types of 'pulao'. One of my favorite pulao is 'Jeera Rice' because of it's saltiness and spicyness. It goes very well with many types of veg and non veg curry. The recipe is very simple and easy. You can also give 'jeera rice' in any adult's lunch box with dry curry, every combo will become great. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/gobi-pokora.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Gobi Pakore / Fulkopir Pokora (Bengali style) / Cauliflower Fritters</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/gobi-pokora.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/gobi-pokora.jpg' />We Indians are crazy about 'pakore' .. don't you think so ?? We make fritters out of almost everything - 'potato', 'eggplant', 'okra', 'cabbage', 'chili', 'lentils', 'chicken', 'fish' and so many more ]]>&#x1f603;<![CDATA[. 'He' adores only two vegetables in his life, one is potato and the other one is cauliflower. You can impress him with any type of cauliflower dish. So, is there any doubt about what I'm talking about ?? Obviously about 'fulkopir pokora' or 'gobi pakore' !! One of our favorite weekday's meal is 'rice', 'veg daal' and these fritters. Generally in two ways you can make these fritters, one - you have to boil the florets before frying and two- you can stir fry them before deep frying like we Bengalis do. Believe me, the taste becomes delicious. You can enjoy your lunch more with these crunchy fritters.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dahi-aloo.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dahi Aloo / Dahiwale Aloo / Potato cooked in yogurt sauce</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dahi-aloo.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dahi-aloo.jpg' />Sometimes, specially in weekdays, I just want to spend very little time in kitchen but also cook some tasty foods. 'Dahi Aloo' is one of the quickest and tastiest maincourse I found out. You have to cook the crumbled and boiled potatoes in a spicy, tangy yogurt sauce. It is that simple, can you imagine ? This is also a no onion and no garlic recipe, best for puja days or 'vrat' days. You can pair this dish with 'poori', 'paratha' or 'roti'. Try this simple recipe in your kitchen and let me know the results ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dallas-trip.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>A short Trip to Dallas</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dallas-trip.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dallas-trip.jpg' />I am a homemaker and a food blogger. Both my husband and me love to eat different food as well as travel various US cities. I was planning to share our travel and food experience with you.
Presently we are staying at Austin and our last trip was to California on June, 2015. You can think of how much bore we were for not going outside Austin for past 7 months. We celebrated 'Durga Puja', 'Christmas', 'New Year' in Austin but something was missing!!! So, I took the initiative and planned a very short trip to the nearest city, Dallas. We both wanted some relaxation and refreshment. Did we get that in Dallas?? WoW, yeaahhh... 
We visited the historic Texas city with lot of cultural heritages and true history of the state. Today I am sharing our experience of Dallas with you. As this is my first travel blog so please let me know if you have any suggestions or feedback.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dim-posto.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sorshe Dim Posto / Egg curry with Mustard and Poppy seeds paste</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dim-posto.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dim-posto.jpg' />We both are not frequent egg eaters, but when we do, we try to make the curry yumm yumm !! One of our favourite egg curry is 'sorshe dim posto'- traditional bengali dish. 'Sorshe' means mustard seeds and 'posto' means poppy seeds. Lunch dishes always plays a big part in Bengali cuisine. There are several typically bengali dishes which you can only enjoy as lunch with steamed rice and may be after that, a long nap. This dish is one of those typical dishes but with a very simple and easy recipe. The fresh flavour of green chilies and poppy seeds always makes us happy. It is my pleasure to share this traditional egg recipe with you guys. Make this in your lunch and enjoy.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/turkish-kebab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sish Kebab / Turkish Kabab</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/turkish-kebab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/turkish-kebab.jpg' />I have tried some middle eastern platters in couple of restaurants at Austin. I have fallen in love with their kebabs. Once you tasted it, you will never forget that unique taste. I also love their shawarma chicken. So, I reasearched how to make those kebabs at home and the easiest one is this 'turkish kebab'. I also mentioned it as 'sish kebab' because in several places I found the same recipe but with this name. Serve them always with mint sauce or tzatziki sauce. After making them, don't get confuse by their names, just enjoy the awesome taste of juicy, succulent kebabs.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kosha-mangsho.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Curry (Tagore family's recipe) / Kosha Mangsho (Thakurbari style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kosha-mangsho.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kosha-mangsho.jpg' />'Thakurbari' means Rabindranath Tagore's home, which is situated at Jorashanko, Kolkata. Tagore's family is popular for many things and one of them is 'cooking'. Nowadays, you can watch plenty of cooking programmes in TV, but when I was in school, only few magazines used to publish cooking recipes on weekends only. The craze was also different in that time. I still can remember how my mom and grandma used to eagerly waited for these kind of magazine recipes. Among them, one of the popular item was 'Thakurbarir Kosha Mangsho', secret recipe of their family. I am not telling you that there is a huge difference between normal mutton kosha and this one, they also told the usual process but with some slight twists. These twists will make the dish more unique and delicious. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely meal with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mach-bhuna.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish curry with green Peas paste / Macher Sobuj Bhuna / Koraishuti bata diye Macher Kaliya</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mach-bhuna.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mach-bhuna.jpg' />Its winter, the season of colourful veggies... One of my favourite veggie is 'green peas' / Koraishuti. You can make so many items with these tiny green balls like, 'matar paneer', 'peas kachori', 'dum aloo with peas', 'khichdi', 'veg daal', 'cabbage curry with peas' etc. But 'fish curry with green peas paste' may seems new to somebody. Its nothing but a dry fish curry with a tasty extra addition of green peas paste - as simple as that. When I was in school, on 1 of my birthday, mom made this special fish curry for me. That was the first and also last time I ate this dish, but still can remember the unique taste. So, two days before I thought to make something new with fish, suddenly remembered about this one. Immediately I gave a call to mom and asked for the recipe. She told me, I followed every line of her and Taaddaaa... a spicy+sweet+tangy fish curry came out from my kitchen. Please let me know how it turns out for you.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-gobi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Aloo Gobi (dhaba style) / Potato and Cauliflower curry / Aloo Fulkopir torkari</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-gobi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/aloo-gobi.jpg' />We, nonvegetarian people, generally ordered nonveg dishes while eating at restaurants or dhabas. But we also love to eat home cooked vegetarian meals. In one of our trip to Digha before marriage, we made a stop at the famous 'Sher-e-punjab' for heavy breakfast. We ate there several times before but never did breakfast, so, that was our first time. As it was morning, we orderd veg like 'aloo paratha', 'aloo gobi', 'roti', 'bhindi masala' and 'lassi'. All of them were delicious but I will never forget the taste of 'aloo gobi'. Oh my god, my mouth is full of water right now !! It was the tasty, spicy and chatpata veg curry I have ever had. Bengalis usually make 'aloo-fulkopi' as a thick runny curry but that was a dry curry and goes best with roti and some salads. You can also give this yummy curry in lunchbox with bread. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/tzatziki-sauce.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Tzatziki Sauce</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/tzatziki-sauce.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/tzatziki-sauce.jpg' />Last month we, two, went for shopping at our nearest outlet mall. We often go there for shopping. A food truck 'Kebabeque' was a new edition to the food court. They served middle eastern food like 'falafel rice', 'hummus', 'shawarma platter' etc. We took a rice bowl with falafel. They served a good amount of flavourful saffron rice, fresh spinach, some good falafel, tasty hummus and tzatziki sauce. We really loved everything in that bowl. But the sauce caught my main attention. It was so fresh, the flavours were unique and added a different taste to the whole bowl. So, after coming home, I started to do research about this 'tzatziki' sauce and I never thought that the ingredients will be so simple. I made this sauce next day with some turkish kebabs and we enjoyed every bite of them. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mix-noodles.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mix Hakka Noodles / Mix Chowmin</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mix-noodles.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mix-noodles.jpg' />Almost every one has a slight weakness over chinese food. Taste and flavour of their food is totally unique. In Kolkata, many street food joints sell chinese food like various types of chowmin, chilli chicken, manchurian, lollipops etc. They all tastes really good. Today I am sharing the delicious recipe of 'mix Hakka noodles'. The dish has lots of vegetables, chicken and also egg, that's why the name is 'mix chowmin'. You can also add your choice of protiens like shrimp, tofu, pork, beef etc. This recipe is very simple and easy. You have to try this in your kitchen.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/ginger-mutton.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Adabata aar kacha-lonkar Mutton / Mutton curry with ginger and green chilies</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/ginger-mutton.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/ginger-mutton.jpg' />Few days before I saw a fantastic picture of mutton curry in facebook. The caption was 'adabata aar kacha lonka diye mutton'. After seeing that picture, I decided to make it on dinner with some steamed rice. As the picture didn't provide the detailed recipe, except ginger and green chilies, I followed my own instinct while making the curry. After finishing, I got a thin, flavorful, tasty gravy and soft, succulent mutton pieces. The fresh flavour of green chilies makes the curry more scrumptious. The recipe is very simple and takes very less time to cook. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-mustard-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sorse bata Maach / Sorshe Maach / Fish Mustard Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-mustard-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-mustard-curry.jpg' />As I am Bengali, my favourite fish curry is this one. My husband is also a huge fan of fish and specially this curry. It goes best with hot plain rice. This is a very easy process and the recipe is pretty simple. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it tastes. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/ros-bora.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Ros Bora / Dumplings in sugar syrup</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/ros-bora.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/ros-bora.jpg' />Spring is coming my friend, spring is coming. In Bengal we celebrate 'makar sankranti' and I know that every part of india celebrates the same festival with different name and food. From childhood, I love this festival. My grandma and ma makes so many varities of food like 'pithe', 'dudh puli', 'bhaja pithe', 'soru chakli', 'ashke', 'patisapta', 'kholachi' etc with their love and affection. Each and every dish becomes perfect. 'Ros bora' is a traditional Bengali sweets and you can enjoy them in any occasion. My father is a big fan of 'ros bora'. The dish needs a little effort but the end result will satisfy you. I made this sweet dish today to celebrate  'makar sankranti'. Hope you will all enjoy this festival with lots of sweets.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/begun-vorta.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Baingan ka Bharta / Begun Bhorta / Smoked eggplant curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/begun-vorta.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/begun-vorta.jpg' />Whenever food has smoked or grilled flavour, there is no second thought about it. Because it has to be tasty. There are so many colorful vegetables available in grocery market during winter. I told you before that my love for winter is only because of food. We can make and also consume without any tension various types of food. Today I am talking about 'eggplant'. Though we both are not big fan of eggplant, but love it in 2/3 forms- 'begun vaja', 'begun pora' and 'begun vorta'. Yess, the recipe is about the last one. 'Baingan bharta' is a very popular dhaba food in India. A simple veggie with loads of flavour will make your dinner a special one. If you can make this bharta properly, the taste will beat any nonveg dish. Just close your eyes and give it a try.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/singara-samosa.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Singara (samosa)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/singara-samosa.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/samosa.jpg' />In India samosa is a very popular appetizer. We call it "singara" in West Bengal. Almost every evening my grandpa brought samosas from roadside shop and they were delicious. Last week I made samosas at home (inspired by my mother and husband) and they came out really tasty. So, please try this recipe at your home and impress your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/whole-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Whole Tandoori Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/whole-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/whole-chicken.jpg' />Last saturday 'he' brought a whole chicken from market. I got really panicked because I have never cooked whole chicken before. Immediately I googled for some ideas. First thought was 'murg mussallam' but then my eyes got stuck to a picture of whole roasted chicken and we both love chicken roast. So, the final decision was 'whole tandoori chicken'. The name itself describes it's scrumptiousness. Everybody loves tandoori chicken, then why not with a whole chicken??]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-chaap.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Chaap</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-chaap.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-chaap.jpg' />One of the most famous dish from Mughlai cuisine is 'Chicken Chaap' and the taste is unbeatable. You will find the actual taste and flavour in few restaurants in Kolkata. After researching for a long time on the authentic recipe of Chicken chaap, here is the way how I made it. This recipe will give you the exact flavour of restaurant style Chaap. This dish should not be eaten as regular meal. It has a rich and thick gravy, goes best with pulao, <a href='http://spicyworld.in/biriyani-tag.html'>biriyani</a>, naan or roti. Try not to avoid any ingredient from the list otherwise you will not achieve the real taste.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-porota.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Aloo ka Paratha / Spicy potato stuffed Bread</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-porota.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/aloo-porota.jpg' />I have many stories about 'aloor porota' in my life. My mom used to give me pure bengali style 'aloor porota' in my lunch box during school life and my friends were always a fan of my lunch box. That was my first story of this porota. When I was in college, we (my family) loved to eat 'dhaba food' during travel. In India, each and every dhaba serve 'aloo ka paratha'. I tasted their paratha many times and they were delicious. The taste was different from my mom's porota. This was the second story. The last one is from my dearest friend Monica. When I was in Jersy, one of my punjabi friend Monica, was an expert in making 'aloo ka paratha'. She literally taught me how to make them. Her paratha tastes heavenly. So, these paratha stories are parts of my life. As my husband doesn't like wheat paratha / atta paratha, I had to make them with flour / maida. You will fall in love with those parathas once you make them. Just give it a try.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-pulao.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Pulao / Murg Pulao</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-pulao.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-pulao.jpg' />One of my favorite weekday's meal is 'chicken pulao', because it takes very less time to cook. The dish is super tasty but very easy. I basically don't need any sides with this pulao, it itself tastes delicious. I only love to add potatoes but if you like other veggies in your pulao, feel free to add. This is also a very good lunch box option for adults and I can guarantee you that the box will return empty everytime without a single complain. You just have to try this in your kitchen.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-puri.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Doi phuchka / Dahi puri Chaat</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/doi-puri.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/doi-puri.jpg' />Do I really need to say anything about this ?? It's 'chaat' !! You can get several types of chaat in India from street vendors. They all are very very tasty. One of the famous chaat in Kolkata is 'doi phuchka'. They fill the phuchkas with spicy potato filling, thick curd mixture, tamarind chutney and sprinkle some chopped onion and coriander leaves .. ssluurrpp ... !!! Now I am staying in USA, so I had to make these kind of 'chaat's at home. But believe me, after making this, you will be finding excuses to make them again and again.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/crab-cake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Crab Cakes / Crab Patties</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/crab-cake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/crab-cake.jpg' />In India I never had crab, because they always scares me. After coming to USA, oneday we went for dinner in a restaurant. 'He' already ordered 'crab cake' as appetizer when I went to restroom. I really got upset after returning because I had no idea that crab cake is made of crab meat only. But when they served two cakes in a plate, the platter really impressed me. The taste was phenomenal and most important they didn't scare me at all. After that dinner I tried it in many other restaurants also and fell in love with crab meat (not whole crab). Last weekend I made these cakes at home and they came out delicious. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-pokora.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Pokora (Pakora) / Chicken Fritters</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-pokora.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-pokora.jpg' />How about a crazy snack in evening?? Ohh yeaah its Pakora time!! This is the perfect 'pokora' recipe ever. In Kolkata we get this kind of chicken pokora from fast food centers. But according to me the best homemade pokora maker is my mom. My friends, our relatives, everyone is a fan of my mom's pokora. They always become spicy, soft, juicy and yummy. If you follow this recipe you can get the same flavour from your pokora.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/daal-bukhara.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Daal Bukhara / Spicy Black Lentils Soup</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/daal-bukhara.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/daal-bukhara.jpg' />I heard a lot about this dish in past few months and started to research. As I never tasted it before, so I went to an Indian restaurant in Austin named 'Bombay Bistro' and tasted their 'daal bukhara'. Oh my god, it was lip smacking good and then I realized why this dal is so famous. Texture of the dal really impressed me a lot. The authentic recipe is very simple and easy but main trick here is the cooking time. The more you cook, the more texture and taste you will get. I made this dal along with butter naan and the combo was heavenly. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turned out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-paratha.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Paratha / Cottage Cheese Bread</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-paratha.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-paratha.jpg' />Everybody loves paneer, right? Specially when there is a spicy paneer stuffing inside a paratha, I am always up for it. This was my first try on 'paneer paratha' and I just nailed it. Believe me it is much easier than 'aloo paratha'. I made those in breakfast with 'chana masala' and the combo was really gorgeous. Parathas came out perfectly crispy and soft. The taste was unforgettable, we enjoyed them a lot. I'm damn sure that 'he' will request me to make them soon again.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-dakbangla.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Dakbunglow Curry / Mutton Dakbangla</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-dakbangla.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-dakbangla.jpg' />'Dakbanglow' means roadside resting house. Travelers used to take rest or halt for a night in those houses. The care taker of those 'bunglow's cooked this curry for their guests. Nowadays these kind of recipes are almost lost but in a few restaurants in Kolkata you can still find this dish. This is a typical bengali recipe and the tastiest dish ever. Once I ate this curry in my aunt's house and I can still remember the taste. The curry has juicy mutton, spicy gravy, flavorful potato and egg .. do you want anything more ?? It goes very well with plain basmati rice. 'Mutton Dakbangla' will be a great hit for Christmas dinner also. Try this in your kitchen and make your meal a special one.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/crispy-squid.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Crispy Fried Calamari (Squid)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/crispy-squid.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/crispy-squid.jpg' />During bachelor life in USA, 'he' went on a trip to Connecticut and had there 'calamari' twice. He just fell in love with the dish. After marriage 'he' insisted me to have fried calamari in a restaurant and I really was not sure about the taste before, so just picked one and put it in my mouth. After that, I, myself finished half of the plate within few seconds. They were that tasty. I wanted to make this calamari for long time, but never got the courage. Last weekend 'he' bought squid from market and cleaned them properly by seeing you tube and told me to make fried calamari. I was really nervous at first but then the end result really satisfied both of us. If you are also a squid lover person like us, please try this in your kitchen and I am sure you will enjoy them too.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/sooji-halwa.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sooji Halwa / Rava Kesari / Semolina Pudding</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/sooji-halwa.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/sooji-halwa.jpg' />The day before yesterday I was craving for some dessert at afternoon. As I didn't have any in my kitchen, had to make it by own. The quickest recipe I found is this one 'Sooji Halwa'. It really takes 20-25 minutes to prepare and tastes awesome. You can make 'halwa' in many colors like white, golden, yellow or orange. But I like my halwa little yellow in color. This was the first time I made halwa at home, really enjoyed while making and obviously eating it!! I love 'rose' flavor in my halwa, you can add cardamom, cinnamon or nutmeg flavors also. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/potato-stew.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Potato Stew / Aloo Moricher torkari</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/potato-stew.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/potato-stew.jpg' />From childhood, whenever I got attacked by cough and cold, my mom used to feed me this 'aloo (potato) moricher torkari' along with some puffed rice / 'muri'. Its nothing but a simple potato curry with mild flavors of 'ghee' and 'morich' / black pepper. According to my mom, the heat of black pepper goes well against cold and cough. Magically my neck always felt better after finishing this mom-made curry. The recipe is very simple but it tastes delicious. Specially you will enjoy this curry during winter along with some luchi (poori) or parathas.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-biriyani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Biriyani</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-biriyani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-biriyani.jpg' />You always have a grand feeling whenever you prnounce the name 'mutton biriyani'. I mean really I need to describe this? It become the most popular indian dish among the world. Biriyani has its own aroma, juicy meat and long grain flavourful rice. But in Kolkata they add boiled potato and egg in their biriyani which makes you more greedy:-) I know that the process is lenthy but believe me you will fall in love with the end result.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-rangeela.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken do Rangeela / Double colored Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-rangeela.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-rangeela.jpg' />First let me thank Disha D'souza for this unique idea. 2-3 weeks ago in a facebook group I saw her unique post and really got inspired. Though I changed the name and recipe little bit (hope she won't mind), but the idea credit must go to Disha.  Lots of love and thanks from 'spicy world' to her. Now lets talk about the dish. You can see this is a double colored chicken curry. I also maintain two different taste with the color. I know you are thinking that the process will be lenthy, believe me its not. The taste is phenomenal and goes very well with rice. You can also serve this with naan, paratha or roti. Try this in your kitchen and make your meal a colourful one.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-wrap.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Tandoori Chicken Wraps</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-wrap.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-wrap.jpg' />Last week, from Monday to Friday, I was very lazy and didn't do much innovative cooking. We really got bored of eating usual meals. So, I thought to do something simple but new in the weekend. I had some boneless chicken and homemade <a href='http://spicyworld.in/tortilla.html'>tortillas</a> in my kitchen. Suddenly planned to make some wraps. But then I was wondering about the flavour of the filling. 'He' suggested to give 'tandoori' flavour and I did it. You will not believe that those were the best wraps I have ever made. They were really scrumptious and will make them soon again. Try this in your kitchen and you will love them too.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/tortilla.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Tortilla</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/tortilla.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/tortilla.jpg' />After coming to Texas I was familiar with the name of 'tortilla'. Here maxican food is very famous. 'Tortilla' plays a big role in mexican cuisin. They make various dishes with this tortilla and many of them tastes really delicious. With tortilla you can make 'taco', 'burrito', 'quesedilla', 'enchilada' etc. I really love each of them and that's why I want to make tortilla in my own kitchen. Usually they use vegetable lard for the dough, as I didn't have that in my home, I used lots of vegetable oil. You can use olive oil also. So, here is how I made my tortillas ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/biuli-daal.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Biulir Daal / Urad daal (Pure bengali style) / Kolaier Daal</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/biuli-daal.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/biuli-daal.jpg' />Soul food means the food which you can enjoy from the bottom of your heart while eating. Being a bengali I always face a common question- 'fish and posto(poppy seeds) are your soul food, right?'. And my answer is always 'oh, hell yaa' ... ]]>&#x1f609;<![CDATA[ Today I will talk about vegetarian food. We always make 'biulir daal' / 'urad daal' with posto. The combo is nothing but heavenly. There is a must ingredient we use in our urad daal is 'hing' / asafoetida. Many bengalis also enjoy this meal with fried eggplant / begunvaja. The recipe is very simple and easy. It is a no onion and no garlic dish. Try this in your kitchen and make your lunch a traditional one.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/khara-masala-mutton.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kata moshlar mangsho / Khara masala mutton</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/khara-masala-mutton.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/khara-masala-mutton.jpg' />Whenever 'he' returns from market and gives me a bag of mutton, it always brings an extra big smile on my face and a great joy in my heart. I guess, this happens to many of you also ]]>&#x1f609;<![CDATA[. I always try to do something new to my mutton curry, because you all know about my experimental nature!! This time I made 'khara masala mutton', the taste was heavenly. After finishing the meal, there were nothing but bones in our plate. 'Khara masala' / 'kata moshla' means whole spices. You don't need to add any ground spices / paste in this curry. I think, this is an Eid special dish in Bangladesh. Always serve this mutton curry with plain rice, in that way you can purely enjoy the juicy mutton pieces with its aromatic gravy. Just give it a try and (I am sure) you will know what I am talking about.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-dopyaza.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Dopyaza / Mutton curry with double onion</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-dopyaza.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-dopyaza.jpg' />In India, 'mutton dopyaza' is a very frequently ordered dish in restaurants. 'Dopyaza' means double amount of onion. From this curry you will get juicy meat, thick gravy and some nice crunch of onions. You can make this curry with chicken and fish also. If you make this dish in any potluck or party, it will become the main attraction. I tried to keep the recipe very simple and easy. Just give it a try.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chinese-fried-rice.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chinese (style) Fried Rice</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chinese-fried-rice.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chinese-fried-rice.jpg' />I guess almost everybody love indo-chinese food. The recipe of this fried rice is also indo-chinese and homemade version. I heard from many foodies that in homemade fried rice, there is always lack of that chinese flavour / restaurant flavour. But after following this recipe, you will forget about this complain. You can serve various side dishes with this kind of 'fried rice'. Try this in your kitchen and let me know about your 'chinese cooking' story.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/jali-kabab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Jali Kabab / Net Kabab (Kebab)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/jali-kabab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/jali-kabab.jpg' />I guess many people are not familiar with this name, believe me, I was also not. 'He' is a big fan of kababs, that's why I always try to find new recipes for kababs. This year, on his birthday, I made these 'jali' kababs. The concept and taste were totally new to us. But luckily 'net kabab' brought a big smile on his face and that was my real satisfaction. 'Jali' means net and they have net like texture. You can make this with mutton / beef / chicken. After trying this I can tell you one thing that you will be finding excuses to make these kababs.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-kofta-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Kofta Curry / Fried Cottage cheese balls curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-kofta-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-kofta-curry.jpg' />Last weekend I wanted to make something new veg maincourse, thats why I chose this 'paneer kofta curry' and it was just delicious. You can make kofta curry with raw banana, jack fruit, chicken, fish, mutton etc. They all tastes really good. I made it with <a href='http://spicyworld.in/paneer-kofta.html'>paneer kofta</a>, you can see how good looking they are and by clicking the picture below you can see how it's prepared.<br/><br/><a href='http://spicyworld.in/paneer-kofta.html'><img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-kofta-curry-1.jpg' /></a><br/><br/>I served this curry with plain rice but you can also serve with naan, kulcha, pulaao, jeera rice or even with paratha. Every combo will make your meal a special one. There are several ways you can make this curry, here is how I made it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-kofta.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Kofta / Fried Cottage Cheese Balls</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-kofta.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-kofta.jpg' />'Kofta' is a very flexible food item, you can serve them as starter or you can soak them in gravy and serve as maincourse also. This was my very first attempt on 'kofta' and from the beginning I was a bit nervous because I often heard that while frying them, kofta has a chance to break. But I carefully maintained the proportion of ingredients and taaddaaa ...!! All of my 'kofta's came out perfectly and they were scrumptious. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-makhani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer Makhani / Paneer Butter Masala / Makhanwala Paneer</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer-makhani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer-makhani.jpg' />'Makhni' is a name of rich, smooth, creamy gravy which is very popular in India. You can make 'chicken makhni', 'paneer makhni', 'kofta curry' and many more dishes with this gravy. I personally love the methi flavour and creaminess about this gravy. We had it in dinner last night with soft butter naans. The combination was heavenly. You just have to try this.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Paneer (Indian Cottage Cheese)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/paneer.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/paneer.jpg' />In vegetarian world 'paneer' plays a very important role. But in nonvegrtarian world it also offers various special dishes. Homemade paneer has its own frshness and taste. There is no comparison between homemade and store bought. I always use homemade fresh 'paneer' in my cooking. You can make several dishes with this. So, try this in your kitchen and I can give you guarantee that you will never buy from store again.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/matar-kachori.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Matar Kachori / Peas Kachori</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/matar-kachori.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/matar-kachori.jpg' />Last tuesday 'he' gave me a call from office at 5:00 pm and requested me to make some 'chatpata' snacks which will go very well with tea. So, I had exactly 1 hour in my hand to make something. Don't know why, but suddenly a thought of spending evening time in India, came in my mind. My grandpa used to bring different kinds of snacks like 'samosa', 'nimki', 'vegetable chop', 'kachori', 'beguni' etc and with all our family members we enjoyed those with a cup of tea and some puffed rice (muri). Those are kind of evenings, which I will miss rest of my life. After so many thoughts, I planned to make 'matar kachori' / peas kachori because I had some frozen peas in my kitchen. The recipe is very easy, simple and tasty. All of my 'kachori'-s came out perfectly and his expression was like ]]>&#x1f44c;<![CDATA[]]>&#x1f44c;<![CDATA[]]>&#x1f44c;<![CDATA[. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy a lovely evening with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chingrir-chop.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chingrir Chop / Shrimp Croquettes</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chingrir-chop.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chingrir-chop.jpg' />This snack is a very popular street food in West Bengal. You will enjoy these croquettes more from small street food shop / gumti / jhupri , though I don't have any experience of eating 'chingrir chop' from any restaurant. In US, there is no 'gumti', thats why I had to make those in my kitchen and brought the exact taste from Bengal. They were really delicious and we enjoyed them with chilli sauce, but you can also serve them with 'kasundi'. There are many ways of making these croquettes, here is how I made them.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/narkel-naroo.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Instant Narkel Naroo / Instant Coconut Nadus</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/narkel-naroo.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/narkel-naroo.jpg' />I know making 'naroo' is a really time consuming task. Specially when you have puja in your house, there are several works to do. Here is the shortcut version of 'naroo', which you can make in 10 minutes. The recipe is so simple and needs very few ingredients. Naroo, made with fresh coconut, tastes heavenly. But believe me you will love these too. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/bhapa-posto.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Bhapa Posto</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/bhapa-posto.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/bhapa-posto.jpg' />I think almost every Bengali is familiar with this name. I love 'posto' or poppy seeds in any form. I made this dish on yesterday lunch along with some steamed rice. The fresh flavour of mustard oil and poppy seed paste always makes me crazy. I made it in microwave but you can also make this in oven. Try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/pulled-chicken-burger.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Pulled Chicken Burger</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/pulled-chicken-burger.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/pulled-burger.jpg' />Here in Texas, one of the famous burger is 'pulled pork burger'. Everyone is a big fan of this burger. Last weekend I had some buns in my kitchen and some boneless chicken in my fridge. Then I thought to replace pork with chicken and some delicious 'pulled chicken burger's along with coke came out from my kitchen. I really love to make different types of burger but this one is my first posting on burger. I will post others soon. Try this easy peasy burger in your kitchen and make your weekend dinner a easy special one.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/baked-spicy-chicken-pasta.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Baked Spicy Chicken Pasta</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/baked-spicy-chicken-pasta.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/baked-spicy-chicken-pasta.jpg' />Its true that I love eating pasta after coming usa. In India I was more fond of noodles, ramen or maggie. But recently I experimented couple of recipes on pasta and they turned out really well. I love my pasta on spicy side, that's why I mentioned it in the title. After baking with cheese, the taste of this dish became phenomenal. If you do not want to bake or use cheese, then make this dish without them. No worries, it also tastes delicious, believe me. You can say this dish is kind of one-pot-meal, usually don't need any sides. I love 'rotini' pasta, you can use 'penne', 'maccaroni', 'shells' or any kind of your choice. Try this in your kitchen and enjoy the meal with your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chana-masala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chana masala / Chole masala (Curry of Garbanzo Beans)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chana-masala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chana-masala.jpg' />I have a friend in New Jersy, Monica, who makes the best chana masala ever. I learned this recipe from her. Since we moved from Jersy I missed her and her cooking very much. This is a punjabi dish, goes very well with <a href='http://spicyworld.in/bhatura.html'>bhatura</a>, puri or roti. The recipe is very simple and it tastes delicious.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/baked-rosogolla.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Baked Rosogolla</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/baked-rosogolla.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/baked-rosogolla.jpg' /><br/><img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/baked-rosogolla-13.jpg' /><br/><br/>'Diwali' is the celebration of light and sound. Its been two years I am away from home (Kolkata). My papa used to buy me lots of crackers a day before diwali, we toast them in sunlight and in the evening of diwali my (maternal) uncle bought me some more crackers for his 'vagni'. Then around 8 pm me and my papa used to decorate our roof with candles and after that we started doing fireworks with our family. Ohh, I almost forgot to tell you about food. My mom used to make various types of sweets at home and we enjoyed them a lot. So, I made 'baked rosogolla' for this diwali, my first attempt and I nailed it. Try this in your kitchen and share some of your diwali story with me.<br/><b>Spicy World wishes everyone a very Happy DiWaLi ...</b>]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-korma.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Korma</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-korma.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-korma.jpg' />When an inch of oil or ghee floats upon gravy, yes its 'mughlai nawabi dish'. 'Nawab' means king. This category of curries have nice colored, rich, thick, creamy gravy. 'Chicken Korma' is my favourite one. You can easily eat this curry once in a month along with 'biriyani', 'pulaao', 'butter naan' or 'rumali roti'. Do not put this kind of food in your regular diet because you have to make or eat korma without any guilt, otherwise you will never enjoy the richness of mughlai food.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-soup.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Soup (Desi Style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-soup.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-soup.jpg' />You know winter is coming and all you need is a bowl of warm soup. You can put many vegetables and protiens in it. Soup is very healthy meal for kids. It is also very helpful for sick people. Specially in winter, you can get many varieties of vegetables from grocery store. Then why not make some soup? This one is a very simple and easy recipe. I mentioned 'desi' style because i used some whole spices (indian) for aroma. Try this in your kitchen and make your winter morning a happy one.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaniya-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dhaniya Chicken / Coriander Chicken / Dhonepata Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaniya-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaniya-chicken.jpg' />When I was in college, I loved to do some cooking with my mom. 'Dhaniya Chicken' was one of my teenage speciality dish. Dhaniya / dhonepata means coriander leaves. I only prefer to use garlic and don't like to use whole spices for this dish. According to me, the strong aroma of whole spices dominate the flavour of fresh coriander leaves. After a long time, last night I made 'dhonepata chicken' along with some steamed rice and enjoyed every moment of prepping, cooking and eating just like those college days ]]>&#x1f60a;<![CDATA[. Try this in your kitchen and share some of your teenage story with me.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-hakka-noodles.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Hakka Noodles</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-hakka-noodles.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-hakka-noodles.jpg' />It is almost impossible to find them who doesn't love chinese food, specially 'hakka noodles'. I think, this is the most frequently ordered dish in any indo-chinese restaurant. I, personally don't like any side dish with hakka noodles because this chinese dish has its own magic. I made this noodles in dinner and the taste turned out exceptionally good, the flavour was same like restaurants. Try this in your kitchen and share your 'noodles story' with me ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-fulkopi-posto.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Aloo Fulkopi Posto (Potato and cauliflower cooked in poppy seed paste gravy)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-fulkopi-posto.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/aloo-fulkopi-posto.jpg' />Bengali without posto(poppy seed)? - impossible. Bengali without aloo(potato)? - no way. I specially can't live without these two. 'Aloo posto' or 'aloo fulkopi posto' is my favourite weekday's lunch with steamed rice and hot daal. My hubby is very fond of 'fulkopi' (cauliflower), that's why I added this in the gravy. But if you don't like you can totally skip this part. The most simple and easy recipe is this one. Here is how I made it ...]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-tandoori.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Tandoori Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-tandoori.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/tandoori-chicken.jpg' />This dish dont need any explanation. Its very popular in India and nowadays all over the world. There was a rumor that without "tandoor/oven" you cannot make tandoori. But believe me today I am sharing "oven method and gas method" of making tandoori chicken. 'Tandoor' means oven made with clay and the heat comes from charcoal. In restaurants the actual tandoor flavour comes when juices of chicken drops on the charcoal, it creats a nice smokey flavour. You will fall in love with this dish. Please give it a try at your home and prove the rumor wrong.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/khatta-baingan.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Khatta Baingan (khatta begun)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/khatta-baingan.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/khatta-baingan.jpg' />'Khatta' means tangy/sour and 'baingan' means eggplant/begun. Most probably this dish is from Kashmiri cuisin. I do not have much knowledge about this cuisin but I can assure you that you will never forget this eggplant recipe. Last wednesday we both wanted to eat veg in dinner and I had an eggplant(begun) in my fridge. So, I googled for some spicy veg recipes made with eggplant, and my eyes got stuck to this one. The recipe is simple and very easy to make. I just made a little change, as 'he' doesn't like tamarind (tetul/imli) in his food, I had to use yogurt instead of it. Believe me the taste came out really delicious. It goes very well with steamed rice or plain roti. Try this in your kitchen and share your story with us.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dry-chicken-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sukha Chicken (Dry Chicken Curry)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dry-chicken-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dry-chicken-curry.jpg' />I always try new recipes on chicken because it is my family's favourite. Last Friday 'he' wanted to eat any dry preparation at dinner and told me 1 and half hour ago from dinner time. As I had not much time in hand, so, I thought how about marinate everything with chicken pieces and cook it. It took very less time and the taste turned out phenomenal. Believe me the end result was beyond my imagination. You have to try this in your kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/niramish-aloo-torkari.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Niramish Aloo Torkari</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/niramish-aloo-torkari.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/niramish-aloo-torkari.jpg' />This is a no onion and no garlic recipe. Usually in many 'puja's we make this kind of dishes. 'Potato curry' goes very well with 'luchi', 'paratha', 'kochuri' etc. But last tuesday I tried a new combo with 'bhatura'. Magically we both loved and enjoyed it very much. I learned this potato curry from my mom. She also follow the same recipe for 'niramish aloo dom' and it tastes always good. Try this new combo and I am sure you will love them too.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-muro-muger-daal.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Macher Muro die Muger Daal (Fish head cooked with spicy lentil soup)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-muro-muger-daal.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-muro-muger-daal.jpg' />This lentil soup is one of the traditional food in Bengal. Last weekend I had two fish heads in my fridge. I am personally not too much fond of plain fish head curry. So, I made this dish and it came out really perfect like 'biyebari'. In most of the bengali wedding this dish is must for lunch and everybody loves it. I ate the home made version of this daal twice from my mom. Those times I really didn't find difference because she made it so tasty and this time 'he' didn't find any difference ]]>&#x1f603;<![CDATA[. Lets see how I made this 'daal' and don't forget to try it in your kitchen.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/bhatura.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Bhatura (with Yeast)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/bhatura.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/bhatura.jpg' />'Chola-Bhatura' is a very popular combo in India and also in many other countries. The origin of this dish is from Punjab. But you can get this combo as street food in Delhi and many other parts of India. I ate and learnt homemade 'chola-bhatura' from my friend Monica, when I lived in New Jersy. Her 'bhatura's always came out very flakey and puffed up. There is nothing but 'super tasty' I can say about her <a href='http://spicyworld.in/chana-masala.html'>chola</a>. I have already posted that recipe. Last night I made bhaturas with <a href='http://spicyworld.in/niramish-aloo-torkari.html'>niramish aloo torkari</a> or <a href='http://spicyworld.in/niramish-aloo-torkari.html'>spicy potato curry</a>. We, two, really loved and enjoyed them. Try this in your kitchen and make your dinner a special one.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kashmiri-dum-aloo.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kashmiri Dum Aloo</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kashmiri-dum-aloo.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kashmiri-dum-aloo.jpg' />From my childhood, almost in every bengali wedding I have seen the famous combo of 'koraishutir kochuri' and 'kashmiri aloor dom' in the menu card. There is no question about that combo, it tastes heavenly. This dish is no onion and no garlic recipe but the attraction is its nice red color. You will need different types of spice powder for this recipe. I don't know much about kashmiri cuisin, this was my first try and I just nailed it ]]>&#x1f60a;<![CDATA[ . I served this curry in dinner with some 'jeera rice' and 'his' reaction was ]]>&#x1f44d;<![CDATA[]]>&#x1f44c;<![CDATA[... Try this in your kitchen and I truly wanna know about your family's response.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-jhol.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Macher Jhol</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-jhol.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/macher-jhol.jpg' />Bengalis make various kinds of fish curry with different types of fishes. The most simple and easy one is 'macher jhol' or fish curry. 'Jhol' means runny version of a curry. This dish is usually served as lunch with steamed rice and we all are fan of it. In 'macher jhol' you can use rohu / katla / tilapia / pomfret / pabda etc. One can add many kinds of vegetables like potato, cauliflower, eggplant, green peas, carrot etc. I always make this dish with potato and cauliflower because of 'him']]>&#x1f609;<![CDATA[. He typically loves this combo. According to me, there is only one restriction about this dish. You have to use 'green chilies' only for the heat and flavour. Try not to use red chili powder or dry red chili because it will make a huge difference. So, here is the recipe how I make 'macher jhol' for my family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/simple-aloor-dom.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Simple Aloor Dom</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/simple-aloor-dom.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/simple-aloor-dom.jpg' />Bengalis are always very fond of 'peas kochuri' and 'aloor dom' (Dum Aloo) during winter. In Texas, the temparature starts falling as we approach towards the winter time. I already took out light blankets, full sleeves and light sweters. Last weekend 'he' begged me for 'kochuri-alurdom' and here is the result ... ]]>&#x1f609;<![CDATA[ I have already posted one recipe of <a href='http://spicyworld.in/dum-aloo.html'>'aloor dom'</a> which we can make for party or any special occasions. But this one, you can eat anyday with 'luchi', 'paratha', 'daalpuri' and very easy to make. Try this in your kitchen and don't forget to share your winter story with us.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/grilled-cheese-sandwich.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Grilled Cheese Sandwich</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/grilled-cheese-sandwich.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/grilled-cheese-sandwich.jpg' />Sandwich without cheese? - boring ]]>&#x1f61f;<![CDATA[ Cheesy gooey sandwich? - total fun ]]>&#x1f603;<![CDATA[ Yes I am talking about grilled cheese sandwich. This one is the most easy sandwich recipe in the world. The choice of cheese is entirely upto you. You can serve this as breakfast and also as evening snack. Your little tummy will enjoy this sandwich everytime. Here, I have done something new. I have posted step by step clicks along with the recipe, so that the process become more lucid for you. Grab a sandwich and enjoy an evening with your loved ones.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-sandwich.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Sandwich</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-sandwich.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-sandwich.jpg' />Who doesn't love sandwich ? When there is chicken, I am always up for it ]]>&#x1f609;<![CDATA[. I make this kind of sandwich in my home oftenly. The taste is kind of Indian spicy but believe me you will love it. One can make many kinds of sandwiches, and this one is my kind. If you have everything in your hand then the process is very simple and easy. You will need '<a href='http://spicyworld.in/chicken-chutney-kabab.html'>green chutney</a>' for the sandwich. Make this in your own kitchen and don't forget to share your sandwich story with me.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/radhaballavi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Radhaballavi</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/radhaballavi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/radhaballavi.jpg' />Almost in every Bengali wedding they serve 'radhaballavi' along with 'aloor dom' as breakfast. 'Radhaballavi' is nothing but deep fried puffed bread stuffed with spicy lentil. It tastes even better with spicy curry and 'rosogolla'. There are many varieties of fried puffed bread like 'daalpuri', 'luchi', 'kochuri' etc and this one is also very tasty. Last night I made it along with potato curry and we all love it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-chutney-kabab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Chutney Kabab</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-chutney-kabab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-chutney-kabab.jpg' />Last weekend I made a jar of coriander-mint chutney and kept in for fridge for future purposes. Yesterday 'he' wanted some snacks in the evening and also wanted something new. Usually we serve kababs along with green chutney but I used that green chutney for the marination of the chicken. Believe me it was worth trying and that's the reason I named it 'chutney kabab'.The texture and taste came out so good that he insisted me to share the recipe with you. Try this at your home and let me know about your story.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-rezala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish Rezala</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-rezala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-rezala.jpg' />'Rezala' means we all know white, creamy, velvety gravy. In restaurants chicken or mutton rezala is very popular. But here is the recipe of mouth watering 'fish rezala' which I ate one of my sister's wedding. There were plenty of delicious items in buffet but 'fish rezala' was the most crowded stall. That was really finger licking good. Recipe is the same as usual 'rezala' type, I just made it with fish. It goes very well with plain rice, jeera rice or pulaao. Try this in your own kitchen and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/makhmali-sondesh.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Makhmali Sondesh</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/makhmali-sondesh.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/makhmali-sondesh.jpg' />This recipe happened by mistake last week. I know what you are thinking!! But I will never regret about this mistake because it turned out delicious. Let me tell you the story first. Last week I took an attempt to make 'sondesh', but the taste came out very less sweeter. I got panicked and immediately called my only life saver 'mom'. She adviced me to follow the process of 'rosmalai'. In rosmalai we put 'rosogolla' in kheer and in my case, I put 'sondesh' in kheer. Magically it became a new, frequently demanded dessert to my family. 'Makhmali' means very soft in hindi. 'Sondesh' will become very soft after adding it in kheer, that's why I named it 'makhmali sondesh'.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dahi-dhuan-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dahi Dhuan Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dahi-dhuan-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dahi-dhuan-chicken.jpg' />It's always very hard for me to make as usual meal like 'daal, sabji' on weekend. I am sure you will get delicious aroma of spicy dishes from my kitchen almost every weekend. Last weekend 'charcoal' flavour was coming out from a new chicken preparation. Yes, its 'dahi dhuan chicken'. If you like to eat dhaba foods then you will become a fan of this dish. It has a thick rich gravy, nice crunch of onion and appetizing smokey flavour. Just close your eyes and go for it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/muri-ghonto.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Muri Ghonto (Fish head with spicy rice)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/muri-ghonto.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/muri-ghonto.jpg' />In Bengali ceremony preparing any dish with fish head is a very good sign. There are plenty of dishes where they use fish head. But 'muri ghonto' is the <b>delicacy of Bengal</b>. I learned this dish from my mom. There are also some variations of muri ghonto. Some uses yellow lentil or flattened rice instead of <b>gobindovog rice</b>. But I prefer this dish what my mom used to make. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-tangri-kabab.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Tangri Kabab</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-tangri-kabab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-tangri-kabab.jpg' />Nowadays 'kabab' become very popular starter in party menu or restaurant's menu. 'Tangri' means leg piece. When we go to restaurants for dinner, this is our must starter. The taste is completely different from tandoori chicken and you will love it. After today you can make this dish in your own kitchen.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/oreo-milkshake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Oreo Milkshake</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/oreo-milkshake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/oreo-milkshake.jpg' />Whenever my tummy craving for sweet snack, Oreo is my first choice. I also love to drink milkshake during summer afternoon. Every friday after returning from office 'he' wants special snacks / drinks. Last friday I made a milkshake with oreo and it was a total hit. Try this in your kitchen and impress your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-stew.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Stew</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-stew.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-stew.jpg' />During summer we generally avoid to eat rich food. But when it comes to mutton, the decision become difficult ]]>&#x1f609;<![CDATA[. For this kind of situation 'mutton stew' is the perfect food for all. The recipe is very simple and have some mild flavours. You will love this when you make it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/pineapple-milkshake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Pineapple Milkshake</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/pineapple-milkshake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/pineapple-milkshake.jpg' />I love the sweetness and juiciness of pineapple in summer. Then why not make a milkshake with this one in a hot afternoon?? Believe me you will love this milkshake more than anything ]]>&#x1f60a;<![CDATA[ ... ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dum-aloo.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dum Aloo</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dum-aloo.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dum-aloo.jpg' />We all love to eat 'aloor dom' along with 'luchi' or 'kochuri'. This is our comfort food. It also goes very well with 'pulao' or 'fried rice'. This one is my mom's recipe. She make the tastiest aloor dom ever. Yesterday I tried this recipe and it came out perfectly.Just give it a try.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/spicy-macaroni-mushroom.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Spicy Macaroni with Mushroom</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/spicy-macaroni-mushroom.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/spicy-macaroni-mushroom.jpg' />Pasta is one of my favourite snack. Last week I had some boiled pasta, cooked sauce and some mushrooms in my fridge. Then I made this dish. I did not follow any particular recipe. But it came out delicious. Make this at your kitchen and surprise your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/omelet-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Omelet Curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/omelet-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/omelet-curry.jpg' />We all love to eat omelet. My grandma used to make this dish with her love and care. That is why it always turned out so tasty. Today I am sharing this recipe with little changes. Please make this at your home.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-mutton-tarka.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mutton Tarka (Dhaba Style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-mutton-tarka.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaba-style-mutton-tarka.jpg' />In India 'dhaba' means roadside food joints. They offer delicious and spicy meals. Among all of their meals, 'tarka-roti' is the famous one. I once ate 'Mutton Tarka' from them and it was super tasty. Last week I try this tarka recipe and reveal that it tastes exactly like 'dhaba tarka'. Just follow the recipe and impress your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-kalia.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Macher Kalia (Different Style)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-kalia.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/macher-kalia.jpg' />We Bengalis are very fond of fish. Our common meal is fish curry and rice. This recipe is one of the fish curry which we make in occasions and gatherings. I already gave you one kaliya recipe and this one is also very tasty. Try this at your home and let me know how it turns out.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-chop-fish-croquettes.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Macher chop (Fish Croquettes)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/macher-chop-fish-croquettes.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/macher-chop-fish-croquettes.jpg' />This is one of my favourite snacks in the evening along with tea. You can get this chop from many fast food centers in West Bengal. But today you can make this Bengali style macher chop in your own kitchen. Just follow the recipe and you will get this mouth watering snack very easily.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dry-chili-fish-mushroom.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dry Chili Fish with Mushroom</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dry-chili-fish-mushroom.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dry-chili-fish-mushroom.jpg' />This is a very simple and easy recipe. You can serve this as starter or maincourse. You can also substitute fish with chicken. It tastes delicious. Try this at your home and tell me about your experience.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-pakora.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Pakora</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-pakora.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-pakora.jpg' />How about a crazy snack in a rainy evening ?? Ohh yeaah its Pakora time!! Many houses have their own pakora story. In Kolkata we get this kind of chicken pakora from fast food centers. If you follow this recipe you can get the same flavour from your homemade pakora.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/stawberry-milkshake.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Strawberry Milkshake</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/stawberry-milkshake.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/stawberry-milkshake.jpg' />How about a chilled milkshake in a crazy hot afternoon?? Everybody will say "yessss" .. Lets do this with the sweet flavour of strawberry.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/lassi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Lassi (Yogurt smoothie)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/lassi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/lassi.jpg' />Lassi is the most popular drink of Punjab, India. Nowadays we can get lassi almost everywhere. This is a very refreshing drink during summer. Flavoured lassi are also easily available in the market. But I personally prefer plain lassi. Just follow this recipe and you will get the best lassi from your kitchen.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-egg-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Dhaba style egg curry</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/dhaba-style-egg-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/dhaba-style-egg-curry.jpg' />In India we all love "dhaba" foods and also we love eggs. Mostly their dishes are spicy. So, today I am sharing this spicy dish with you. Please try this at your home.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kasuri-methi-murg-masala.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kasuri Methi Murg Masala</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kasuri-methi-murg-masala.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kasuri-methi-murg-masala.jpg' />I made this dish yesterday and it was a blast. So, I am sharing this recipe with you. Please give it a try and let me know about your experience.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/vegetable-biriyani.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Vegetable Biriyani</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/vegetable-biriyani.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/vegetable-biriyani.jpg' />This dish dont need any explanation. Because its 'Biriyani'. This is the most popular dish in India. The  vegetarian version of biriyani is also very tasty Just give a try and impress your family.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/baked-chicken-legs.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Baked Chicken Legs</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/baked-chicken-legs.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/baked-chicken-legs.jpg' />Wanna try something new ? Just follow this recipe and get perfect starter for your friday evening. These baked leg pieces will never fail to satisfy your apetite. Try this and surprise your family and guest.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/matar-paneer-pulaao.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Matar Paneer Pulaao</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/matar-paneer-pulaao.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/matar-paneer-pulaao.jpg' />First time I ate this pulao from one of my favourite aunt. She can turn this simple pulao into something special with her love and care. She really has some magic in her hand and I simply love it. In many gatherings you can make this dish and impress your guest.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/palak-kichdi.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Palak Kichdi</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/palak-kichdi.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/palak-kichdi.jpg' />When you are in a mood of healthy eating, just give it a try ... You will find peace during eating this khichdi because it has some mild flavours and healthy ingredients. This is a meal which you can not ignore.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kadai-paneer.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kadai Paneer</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kadai-paneer.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kadai-paneer.jpg' />Though me and my hubby both are nonveg lovers, but we also love spicy veg dishes. 'Kadai Paneer' is our favourite one. Last night my dinner was this paneer dish along with butter naan. There were no other words but 'delicious and mouth watering' about the combination. The main attraction here is KADAI masala. It gives such a nice flavour in this dish. Just close your eyes and go for it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/musur-daaler-bora.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Musur daaler Bora (Red lentil fritters)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/musur-daaler-bora.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/musur-daaler-bora.jpg' />According to me comfort food means hot plain rice, lentil soup (daal), one lemon slice, mashed potato with fried onion, one green chili and lots of 'red lentil fritters'. I know every person has their own comfort food. But isn't it become more comforter when your mom serve this plate with her love and care. It definitely is. I learned this recipe from her. Just give it a try.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/watermelon-smoothie.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Watermelon Smoothie</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/watermelon-smoothie.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/watermelon-smoothie.jpg' />I love to eat chilled watermelon cubes during summer. My divaai(grandma) serve watermelon cubes with some crushed ice on top and then magically the taste level increases twice. She has her own unique style. So, today I made an attempt on watermelon smoothie and it came out quite delicious. Hope you will like it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-dak-bunglow.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Dakbunglow / Dakbangla</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-dak-bunglow.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-dak-bunglow.jpg' />Yesterday morning during surfing net I saw an eyecatching picture of Chicken Dak Bunglow curry. It made me doing immediate preparation for dinner.Trust me, after dinner there was literally nothing in our plate except bones:-) It became so damn tasty ! I once ate the mutton version of this curry. That was also finger licking delicious, will upload that soon. Do give this recipe a try and I am sure you will never regret it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/banana-smoothie.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Banana Smoothie</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/banana-smoothie.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/banana-smoothie.jpg' />Whoever like me love to eat banana, this drink is for them. This is a very healthy drink for summer. This needs very few ingredients. Hope you will like it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-kaliaa.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fish Kaliaa</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fish-kaliaa.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fish-kaliaa.jpg' />In Bengali's weekdays lunch menu fish has to be there. There is a say 'mache-bhate-bangali' indicates our common meal is fish curry and rice. This is a special dish for party, occasions or gatherings. Macher kaliya goes very well with sweet pulao, fried rice or even plain rice. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Simple Murgir Jhol (Chicken Curry)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-curry.jpg' />I am an inborn chicken lover. During summer it is not always healthy to eat spicy chicken preparations. For this reason my mom used to make this simple jhol / curry for me. It tastes really good with plain hot rice or plain roti. Give it a try.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-posto.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Aloo Posto (Potato with Poppy seed gravy)</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/aloo-posto.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/aloo-posto.jpg' />Whenever you are going to describe anything about Bengali, you have to mention 'posto'/poppy seeds. They make planty of dishes with posto like 'piyaj posto', 'potol posto', 'posto bora' etc and they all are my favourite dishes. 'Aloo Posto' is one of the popular item among the posto category. You will love to eat this with hot plain rice and daal.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-salad-sandwich.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Salad Sandwich</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-salad-sandwich.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-salad-sandwich.jpg' />I learned this recipe from one of my friend. When I lived in New Jersy she used to make this sandwich for her kid. This is a really healthy breakfast. You can make this any time at your home.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-smoothie.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Mango Smoothie</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mango-smoothie.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mango-smoothie-new.jpg' />This is a very refreshing drink in summer. In India we call this Mango Lassi. My favourite summer fruit is mango. You can make many kinds of drink, dessert with mango.  So let's try this.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/fried-rice.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Fried Rice</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/fried-rice.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/fried-rice.jpg' />There are many varities of fried rice you can make like 'chinese style', 'indian style', 'fried rice with sauce' etc. This recipe is about indian style. This is a complete meal with vegetables. You can add chicken, egg, prwan, mushroom in this dish. You will love this dish.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-roll.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken Roll</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-roll.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-roll.jpg' />This is an awesome non vegetarian snack item. You can also say its a complete snack because it has chicken and paratha. Hope you will like it.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-chicken-chowmein.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Egg Chicken Chowmein</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/egg-chicken-chowmein.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-chow.jpg' />In India we make chinese food with some own variations, that's why we call it 'indo-chinese'. Egg chicken chowmin is very famous street food from kolkata. You can also get veg chowmin, prawn chowmin, only chicken chowmin etc. But my favourite is this one. Try this at your home, you will get the exact taste of street food. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-kali-mirch.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Chicken kali mirch</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/chicken-kali-mirch.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/chicken-kali-mirch.jpg' />I got this recipe from one famous cooking channel in youtube. So, let me thank them first. Now the main attraction of this chicken curry is its aroma and simpleness. When I was making it, the aroma from the spices made my husband and me very much impatient. But anyway we had to wait till dinner and enjoyed with hot roti a lot. Make this dish and I am sure it will become your favourite too.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/kadai-chicken.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Kadai Chicken</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/kadai-chicken.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/kadai_chicken.jpg' />Whenever you are unable to think of any maincourse dish for your party, you can blindly rely on this chicken curry. Everyone will like it. This curry has nice aroma of 'kadai masala', little crunch of onion, capsicum and the juicy chicken pieces. Serve this curry with pulao or biriyani, then your party menu will be memorable. ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-curry.html</guid>
            <author>contact@spicyworld.in (Spicy World by Arpita)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 00:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <title>Sunday's Mutton Curry / Robibarer Mangshor Jhol / Mutton er Laal-Jhol</title>
            <link>http://www.spicyworld.in/mutton-curry.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src='http://spicyworld.in/recipeimages/mutton-jhol.jpg' />Traditional Bengali lunch on sunday is this mutton curry along with plain rice, raw onion chunks and green chilies. After lunch we need a long nap (bhaat ghum). There was a say that we Bengalis can not eat food without potato. This is true. You have to add potatoes to this dish because there are many people like me and my husband who likes potatoes more than mutton pieces specially in this curry.  As a Bengali its my pleasure to share this recipe with you. *Note: you must take that special bhaat ghum otherwise you will feel incomplete.]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
